<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>Innate Technique Feats</name>
		<description>Innate Technique Feats from JJK.</description>
		<author url="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1eC8tEMHnupOuaX6At1X8JORz5iarNe6I-A7j2QzScrE/edit?tab=t.0">JJK</author>
		<update version="6.0.0">
			<file name="innatetechnique-feats.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innatetechnique-feats.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

    <!-- Antigravity System -->
    <element name="Levitation System" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_LEVITATION_SYSTEM">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Gravity Field</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ANTIGRAVITY_SYSTEM_GRAVITY_FIELD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Gravity Field</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 2 CE, you can cast Levitate. You can spend an additional 2 CE to force the creature to make the save at disadvantage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, you can cast Levitate. You can spend an additional 2 CE to force the creature to make the save at disadvantage.</description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_LEVITATE" />
        </rules>
	</element>

    <element name="Dense Antigravity Shield" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DENSE_ANTIGRAVITY_SHIELD">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Antigravity Shield</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ANTIGRAVITY_SYSTEM_ANTIGRAVITY_SHIELD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Antigravity Shield</em></p>
			<p>For an additional 3 CE, your Antigravity Shield instead reduces all damage against you by half your Antigravity's maximum height fall damage dice until the beginning of your next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For an additional 3 CE, your Antigravity Shield instead reduces all damage against you by half your Antigravity's maximum height fall damage dice until the beginning of your next turn.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Antigravitational Flight" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ANTIGRAVITATIONAL_FLIGHT">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Boosted System</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ANTIGRAVITY_SYSTEM_BOOSTED_SYSTEM</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Boosted System</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 3 CE, you can give yourself or another creature you touch a 60 feet hover speed for 10 minutes.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, you can give yourself or another creature you touch a 60 feet hover speed for 10 minutes.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <!-- Auspicious Beast Summon -->
    <element name="Double Up" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DOUBLE_UP">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Auspicious Beast #1: Kaichi</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AUSPICIOUS_SUMMON_KAICHI</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Auspicious Beast #1: Kaichi</em></p>
			<p>Your proficiency with your technique and bond with Kaichi improves. You can summon up to two Kaichi horns at the same time as part of your action. This lets you make an additional attack with your horns.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can summon up to two Kaichi horns at the same time as part of your action. This lets you make an additional attack with your horns.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Zero Friction" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ZERO_FRICTION">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Auspicious Beast #2: Reiki</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AUSPICIOUS_SUMMON_REIKI</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Auspicious Beast #2: Reiki</em></p>
			<p>Your proficiency with your technique and bond with Reiki improves. While your movement speed is increased by Reiki, you gain a +3 bonus to AC and don't provoke opportunity attacks.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While your movement speed is increased by Reiki, you gain a +3 bonus to AC and don't provoke opportunity attacks.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Kirin's Flames" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_KIRINS_FLAMES">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Auspicious Beast #3: Kirin</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_AUSPICIOUS_SUMMON_KIRIN</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Auspicious Beast #3: Kirin</em></p>
			<p>Your proficiency with your technique reaches a crescendo, and your bond with Kirin improves. Whenever a creature hits you with a melee attack while you have Kirin activated, you can force them to take fire damage equal to twice the damage taken.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Whenever a creature hits you with a melee attack while you have Kirin activated, you can force them to take fire damage equal to twice the damage taken.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <!-- Black Bird Manipulation -->
    <element name="All Seeing" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ALL_SEING">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Crow</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLACK_BIRD_CURSED_CROWS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Crow</em></p>
			<p>You have improved your ability to manage information. While you see through the crows you don't gain the blinded condition.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While you see through the crows you don't gain the blinded condition.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Scavenger" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SCAVENGER">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Omen of Death</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLACK_BIRD_OMEN_OF_DEATH</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Omen of Death</em></p>
			<p>You have learned from the opportunistic way of the crows. After attacking a frightened creature you gain temporary hit points equal to your proficiency bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>After attacking a frightened creature you gain {{proficiency}} temporary hit points.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Kamikaze" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_KAMIKAZE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Bird Strike</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLACK_BIRD_BIRD_STRIKE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Bird Strike</em></p>
			<p> Through trial and error, your mastery over Bird Strike has reached new heights. Whenever you use Bird Strike you can choose between either increasing the damage die to d12 instead of d10, or to roll an additional d6 to damage a limb.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Whenever you use Bird Strike you can choose between either increasing the damage die to d12 instead of d10, or to roll an additional d6 to damage a limb.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <!-- Blazing Courage -->
    <element name="Ferocious Courage" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEROCIOUS_COURAGE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Ignition</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLAZING_COURAGE_IGNITION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ignition</em></p>
			<p>Once per turn, you can choose to deal additional fire damage equal to your proficiency bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Once per turn, you can choose to deal {{proficiency}} additional fire damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Blazing Heart" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLAZING_HEART">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Mantle of Courage</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLAZING_COURAGE_MANTLE_OF_COURAGE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Mantle of Courage</em></p>
			<p>When you use Mantle of Courage, all creatures of your choice in range gain 5 temporary hit points and again at the start of your turn for the duration.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use Mantle of Courage, all creatures of your choice in range gain 5 temporary hit points and again at the start of your turn for the duration.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Soulfire" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SOULFIRE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Eternal Flames</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLAZING_COURAGE_ETERNAL_FLAMES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Eternal Flames</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to burn even the soul. When you hit with a melee attack, you can spend 3 CE to cause all fire damage dealt on your turn to ignore immunity to fire damage and reduce a creature's maximum hit points until they complete a long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you hit with a melee attack, you can spend 3 CE to cause all fire damage dealt on your turn to ignore immunity to fire damage and reduce a creature's maximum hit points until they complete a long rest.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Technique Release" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TECHNIQUE_RELEASE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Conflagration</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLAZING_COURAGE_MAXIMUM_CONFLAGRATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Conflagration</em></p>
			<p>When you hit with an attack while Ignition is activated, you can release the technique, ending the effects of Ignition on the weapon in exchange for doubling your fire damage for this attack. If used with Maximum: Conflagration, it instead deals a number of additional damage die equal to the CE spent on Ignition.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you hit with an attack while Ignition is activated you can end the effects of Ignition on the weapon in exchange for doubling your fire damage for this attack. If used with Maximum: Conflagration, it instead deals a number of additional damage die equal to the CE spent on Ignition.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <!-- Blood Manipulation -->
    <element name="Blood Production" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLOOD_PRODUCTION">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Blood Manipulation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION||ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROT_ROT_TECHNIQUES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Blood Manipulation</em></p>
			<p>You have found a way to link your blood and Cursed Energy supply. For 1 CE, you can create a sufficient source of blood for 10 HP.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 1 CE, you can create a sufficient source of blood for 10 HP.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Poisonous Blood" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_POISONOUS_BLOOD">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Blood Manipulation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Blood Manipulation</em></p>
			<p>Your blood has grown to be harmful to others. If you hit a creature by 5 or more than their AC or a creature fails a save against a Blood Manipulation technique by 5 or more, the target is poisoned for 1 minute. They can make a Constitution save at the end of their turn to cure the condition.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>If you hit a creature by 5 or more than their AC or a creature fails a save against a Blood Manipulation technique by 5 or more, the target is poisoned for 1 minute. They can make a Constitution save at the end of their turn to cure the condition.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Blood Crystallization" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLOOD_CRYSTALIZATION">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Blood Constructs</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION_BLOOD_CONSTRUCTS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Blood Constructs</em></p>
			<p> You gain the ability to harden your blood to a solid, even if it risks thrombosis and further increases your versatility. As a bonus action for 3 CE. you gain the following for 1 minute:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>As a reaction, you can add a +5 to your AC against an attack.</li>
                <li>Your unarmed damage dice increases by two levels (d8-d10-d12-2d8)</li>
                <li>You gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>At the end of the duration, you take 2d10 necrotic damage as your blood returns to its normal state.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, for 1 minute you can as a reaction add +5 to your AC against an attack, your unarmed damage dice increases by two levels, and you gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage. At the end of the duration, you take 2d10 necrotic damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Flowing Red Scale: Stack" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FLOWING_RED_SCALE_STACK">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Flowing Red Scale</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION_FLOWING_RED_SCALE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Flowing Red Scale</em></p>
			<p> The power of the Flowing Red Scale has reached new heights. As a bonus action for 6 CE or while Flowing Red Scale is active for 3 CE, you instead gain the following benefits for 1 minute:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Your movement speed is tripled.</li>
                <li>You gain a +4 bonus to AC.</li>
                <li>You have advantage on Dexterity and Strength saving throws and Strength checks and once per round you can reroll a check or save.</li>
                <li>You gain one extra action and reaction.</li>
            </ul>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 6 CE or while Flowing Red Scale is active for 3 CE, you instead gain the following benefits for 1 minute: Your movement speed is tripled, you gain a +4 bonus to AC, you have advantage on Dexterity and Strength saving throws and Strength checks, and you gain one extra action and reaction.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Supernova" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SUPERNOVA">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Piercing Blood</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION_PIERCING_BLOOD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Piercing Blood</em></p>
			<p>You can create small orbs of condensed blood that explode like a buckshot. As an action, you condense your Piercing Blood into a tiny orb of blood in an unoccupied space that you can see within 30 feet, which stays there for a maximum of 1 minute before exploding. You can create as many orbs as your proficiency bonus in an action with each having its own cost, spending 5 CE and 5 HP for each, and can choose for them to explode immediately upon creation or manually as a reaction to a creature entering the range of explosion.</p>
            <p class="indent"> The orb then explodes, forcing every creature within 10 feet of it to make a Dexterity saving throw for each orb. On a failure, the target takes 8d8 piercing damage and is knocked prone. On a success, they take half as much damage and aren't knocked prone.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 CE and 5 HP, create up to {{proficiency}} orbs of blood, spending CE and HP for each one, in an unoccupied space that you can see within 30 feet which stays there for a maximum of 1 minute before exploding. You can choose for them to explode immediately or as a reaction to a creature entering the range of explosion. When a orb explodes each creature within 10 feet of it makes a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, the target takes 8d8 piercing damage and is knocked prone. On a success, they take half as much damage and aren't knocked prone.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Wing King Imitation" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WING_KING_IMITATION">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Piercing Blood</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BLOOD_MANIPULATION_PIERCING_BLOOD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Piercing Blood</em></p>
			<p>You condense your blood into wings resembling veins as a bonus action for 10 CE, gathering the wings behind you and gaining the following benefits for 1 minute:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Your walking speed is quadrupled.</li>
                <li>You gain a flying speed equal to half your walking speed.</li>
                <li>As a free action on your turn, you can unleash lines of blood. This takes shape as three ranged Cursed Energy attacks against a creature within 60 feet. Each attack deals 3d10 + your CE modifier in necrotic damage.</li>
            </ul>
            <p class="indent">While using Wing King, you cannot use Piercing Blood.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, for 1 minute your walking speed is quadrupled, you gain a {{speed}}/2 flying speed, and as a free action on your turn make 3 ranged CE attacks against a creature within 60 feet. Each attack deals 3d10 + {{ce:modifier}} necrotic damage. While using Wing King, you cannot use Piercing Blood.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Boogie Woogie -->
    <element name="Boogie Down" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BOOGIE_DOWN">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Boogie</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BOOGIE_WOOGIE_BOOGIE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Boogie</em></p>
			<p> Your Boogie has increased in speed and the unpredictability of your Boogie. You gain 2 additional reactions which can only be used to Boogie. Additionally, when you Boogie the next attack made against you has disadvantage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You gain 2 additional reactions which can only be used to Boogie. When you Boogie the next attack made against you has disadvantage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Beguiling Tactics" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BEGUILING_TACTICS">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Woogie</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BOOGIE_WOOGIE_WOOGIE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Woogie</em></p>
			<p>The tricky timing and misdirection with Woogie has improved. After getting swapped, the enemy creature must make an Intelligence save or be stunned until the end of their next turn. On a success, they gain advantage on future saves. Additionally, as an action you can fake clap, forcing them to make an Insight check versus your Deception or Performance. On a failure, they waste their next attack by attacking in the wrong direction.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>After getting swapped, enemy creatures must make an Intelligence save or be stunned until the end of their next turn. On a success, they gain advantage on future saves. As an action you can fake clap, forcing them to make an Insight check versus your Deception or Performance. On a failure, they waste their next attack by attacking in the wrong direction.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Best Friend" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BEST_FRIEND">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Round of Applause</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BOOGIE_WOOGIE_ROUND_OF_APPLAUSE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Round of Applause</em></p>
			<p>Boogie Woogie, as effective as it is in solo combat, only reaches its full potential not with an ally, but with a best friend. At the start of combat, you can choose one ally as a Best Friend. When fighting with that ally, you gain the following benefits:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>When you switch the place of your Best Friend with an ally who was previously in melee range of an enemy, on top of advantage, the attack will have its critical range increased by 3.</li>
				<li>Swapping your Best Friend has no cost.</li>
				<li>When flanking with your Best Friend, you and your Best Friend gain a bonus to damage rolls equal to your proficiency bonus.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>At the start of combat, you can choose one ally as a Best Friend. When fighting with that ally, when you switch the place of your Best Friend with an ally who was previously in melee range of an enemy, the next attack will have its critical range increased by 3, swapping your Best Friend has no cost, and when flanking with your Best Friend, you and your Best Friend gain a + {{proficiency}} bonus to damage rolls.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Body Manipulation -->
    <element name="Flawless Acting" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FLAWLESS_ACTING">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Graverobber</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BODY_MANIPULATION_GRAVEROBBER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Graverobber</em></p>
			<p>Your acting skills from hopping bodies transfer to other uses. You must spend seven days and 25 gp to establish the history, profession, and affiliations for an identity. You can't establish an identity that belongs to someone else. For example, you might acquire appropriate clothing, letters of introduction, and official-looking certification to establish yourself as a member of a trading house from a remote city so you can insinuate yourself into the company of others.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You must spend seven days and 25 gp to establish the history, profession, and affiliations for an identity. You can't establish an identity that belongs to someone else.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Memory Bank" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MEMORY_BANK">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Skill Theft</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BODY_MANIPULATION_SKILL_THEFT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Skill Theft</em></p>
			<p>Memories fade and wane, you however have grown beyond that. You remember everything you experience, and you can store them in objects allowing anyone who touches them to experience them from your point of view.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You remember everything you experience, and you can store them in objects allowing anyone who touches them to experience them from your point of view.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Backup" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BACKUP">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Immortality</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_BODY_MANIPULATION_IMMORTALITY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Immortality</em></p>
			<p>As much as you might as well be immortal, it never hurts to be prepared. As an action, after having a dead body prepared, you can prepare it as a backup. This backup works the same as the Clone spell, without the cost or time requirement.</p>
			<div class="reference">
				<div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_CLONE" />
			</div>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>After having a dead body prepared, you can prepare it as a backup. This backup works the same as the Clone spell, without the cost or time requirement.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CLONE" />
		</rules>
	</element>
	
	<!-- Clone -->
    <element name="Meant to be Expendable" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MEANT_TO_BE_EXPENDABLE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have One Man Army</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CLONE_ONE_MAN_ARMY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have One Man Army</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction to damage, you can spend 4 CE to summon a Clone, which shoves you 5 feet and takes the damage in your place.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>As a reaction to damage, you can spend 4 CE to summon a Clone, which shoves you 5 feet and takes the damage in your place.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Unstoppable Legion" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_UNSTOPPABLE_LEGION">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Three is a Crowd</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CLONE_THREE_IS_A_CROWD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Three is a Crowd</em></p>
			<p>You have trained extensively in fighting together with your Clones, gaining the following benefits:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>When flanking with a Clone, you deal additional damage equal to your proficiency bonus.</li>
				<li>You can create Clones as a bonus action for 1 extra CE per clone.</li>
				<li>When one of your Clones is reduced to 0 hit points, rather than waiting 1 minute, you only need to wait 1 round.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When flanking with a Clone, you deal {{proficiency}} additional damage. You can create Clones as a bonus action for 1 extra CE per clone. When one of your Clones is reduced to 0 hit points, rather than waiting 1 minute, you only need to wait 1 round.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Conga Line" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_CONGA_LINE">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Four is a Party</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CLONE_FOUR_IS_A_PARTY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Four is a Party</em></p>
			<p>You can spend 8 CE as a free action to tag team an enemy with your Clones, making a Conga Line on your way to stomp them. You and all clones can immediately move 30 feet and take the attack action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>You can spend 8 CE as a free action to allow you and all clones to immediately move 30 feet and take the attack action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Comedian -->
    <element name="Lasting Laughs" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_LASTING_LAUGHS">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Comedy</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_COMEDY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Comedy</em></p>
			<p>Even when you're the one telling the joke, you can't stop laughing. For an additional 2 CE when you activate Comedy, you can make the technique last 10 minutes. This does not work with Peak Comedy.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For an additional 2 CE when you activate Comedy, you can make the technique last 10 minutes. This does not work with Peak Comedy.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Super Gag" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SUPER_GAG">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Commit to the Bit</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_COMMIT_TO_THE_BIT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Commit to the Bit</em></p>
			<p>You have stepped up your game with some premium material you read online. You gain the following gags while your technique is active:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Written on your Face.</strong> As an action for 3 CE, you target a creature within 30 ft that you can see. For 1 minute or when your technique ends, the target's emotions and intentions are literally written on their face. The target has disadvantage on attacks against anyone who can see their face. Anyone that can see their face knows their general emotions and can tell whenever they are scheming or planning something by reading the doodles on their face.</li>
				<li><strong>Costume Switch.</strong> As an action for 2 CE, you apply a wardrobe change to a number of creatures equal to your CE modifier within 30 ft of you that you can see. This effect is purely cosmetic and cannot change their AC or movement and cannot give them any conditions. You can also change a property about them, such as giving them multiple eyes or arms. These changes are nonfunctional and a creature can take an action to make a Wisdom (Perception) or Intelligence (Investigation) against your CE save DC inspect these changes. On a success, they realize the changes are fake. This feature lasts for a number of minutes equal to your CE modifier before disappearing.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While your technique is active, you can use Written on your Face and Costume Switch.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_WRITTEN_ON_YOUR_FACE" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_COSTUME_SWITCH" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Written on your Face" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_WRITTEN_ON_YOUR_FACE">
		<description>
			<p>As an action for 3 CE, you target a creature within 30 ft that you can see. For 1 minute or when your technique ends, the target's emotions and intentions are literally written on their face. The target has disadvantage on attacks against anyone who can see their face. Anyone that can see their face knows their general emotions and can tell whenever they are scheming or planning something by reading the doodles on their face.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, target a creature within 30 ft that you can see. For 1 minute or when your technique ends, the target has disadvantage on attacks against anyone who can see their face. Anyone that can see their face knows their general emotions and can tell whenever they are scheming or planning something.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Costume Switch" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_COSTUME_SWITCH">
		<description>
			<p>As an action for 2 CE, you apply a wardrobe change to a number of creatures equal to your CE modifier within 30 ft of you that you can see. This effect is purely cosmetic and cannot change their AC or movement and cannot give them any conditions. You can also change a property about them, such as giving them multiple eyes or arms. These changes are nonfunctional and a creature can take an action to make a Wisdom (Perception) or Intelligence (Investigation) against your CE save DC inspect these changes. On a success, they realize the changes are fake. This feature lasts for a number of minutes equal to your CE modifier before disappearing.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, apply a wardrobe change to up to {{ce:modifier}} creatures within 30 ft of you that you can see. This effect is purely cosmetic. These changes are nonfunctional and a creature can take an action to make a Wisdom (Perception) or Intelligence (Investigation) against your CE save DC to inspect these changes. On a success, they realize the changes are fake. This feature lasts for {{ce:modifier}} minutes.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

    <element name="Maximum: Laugh Track" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_LAUGH_TRACK">
    	<prerequisite>Must have Peak Comedy</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_COMEDIAN_MAXIMUM_PEAK_COMEDY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
      	<description>
        	<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Peak Comedy</em></p>
			<p>As a bonus action for 3 CE while your technique is active, you summon an invisible audience around you. For the next minute, creatures within 30 ft have disadvantage on saves against your techniques and you have advantage on ability checks and saves to maintain your technique.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE while your technique is active, for the next minute, creatures within 30 ft have disadvantage on saves against your techniques and you have advantage on ability checks and saves to maintain your technique.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Construction -->
	<element name="Subtle Constructs" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SUBTLE_CONSTRUCTS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Construct</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONSTRUCTION_CONSTRUCT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Construct</em></p>
			<p>After creating an item, you can make a Sleight of Hand check against a creature's passive Perception. On a success, your first attack or check using this creation has advantage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>After creating an item, you can attempt a Sleight of Hand check vs passive Perception to gain advantage on your first attack or check with it.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Imbue" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_IMBUE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Creation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONSTRUCTION_CURSED_CREATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Creation</em></p>
			<p>You have broken down your ability to create a cursed tool into its very essence, including imbuing cursed techniques into objects. At twice the cost of the normal creation of a Cursed Tool, you can imbue an existing item with that cursed tool's Technique for one week. At 6th level this becomes 2 weeks, 3 weeks at 11th level, and a month at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>At twice the cost of the normal creation of a Cursed Tool, you can imbue an existing item with that cursed tool's Technique for one week.</description>
			<description level="6">At twice the cost of the normal creation of a Cursed Tool, you can imbue an existing item with that cursed tool's Technique for two weeks.</description>
			<description level="11">At twice the cost of the normal creation of a Cursed Tool, you can imbue an existing item with that cursed tool's Technique for three weeks.</description>
			<description level="18">At twice the cost of the normal creation of a Cursed Tool, you can imbue an existing item with that cursed tool's Technique for one month.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Perfect Sphere" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_PERFECT_SPHERE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Insectoid Armor</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONSTRUCTION_INSECTOID_ARMOR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Insectoid Armor</em></p>
			<p> Through research and creativity, you have created a Perfect Sphere with no contact area which generates infinite pressure. As an action for 10 Cursed Energy, you create a 10-foot diameter perfect sphere of metal that appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within 10 feet of you and lasts for 1 minute while concentrating. Any creature that touches or ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 8d12 force damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
			<p class="indent">As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn. When you move the sphere, it destroys all barriers and non-magical structures in its way.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 Cursed Energy, create a 10-foot diameter sphere that appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within 10 feet of you and lasts for 1 minute while concentrating. Any creature that touches or ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 8d12 force damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn. When you move the sphere, it destroys all barriers and non-magical structures in its way.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Contractual Recreation -->
	<element name="Surprise Present" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SURPRISE_PRESENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Quick Spender</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONTRACTUAL_RECREATION_QUICK_SPENDER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Quick Spender</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction against any hostile action taken against you, you can materialize one of your receipts for twice the cursed energy cost in a surprise attack. If using an object, you force the creature to make a Dexterity saving throw at disadvantage if they are within range. On a failure, they take bludgeoning damage depending on the object's size. On a success, the creature takes half as much damage. If using a weapon, you can make an attack with the weapon against the attacker at advantage if they are within range. At 11th level, this can be used with Contractual Control with only the one Object or Weapon used as part of this reaction.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>As a reaction against any hostile action taken against you, you can attack with a receipt for twice the CE cost. If using an object, you force the creature to make a Dexterity saving throw at disadvantage if they are within range. On a failure, they take bludgeoning damage depending on the object's size. On a success, the creature takes half as much damage. If using a weapon, you can make an attack with the weapon against the attacker at advantage if they are within range. </description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Bulk Buyer" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BULK_BUYER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Splurge</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONTRACTUAL_RECREATION_SPLURGE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Splurge</em></p>
			<p>You've learned that buying in bulk can lead to a sale! When you use two or more receipts as part of the same action, the CE costs are each reduced by 1 for every receipt you use (minimum cost of 1). If the receipts are of the same type, you gain advantage on attack rolls and ability checks using those creations for 1 minute.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use two or more receipts as part of the same action, the CE costs are each reduced by 1 for every receipt you use (minimum cost of 1). If the receipts are of the same type, you gain advantage on attack rolls and ability checks using those creations for 1 minute.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Master of Receipts" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MASTER_OF_RECEIPTS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Contractual Control</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CONTRACTUAL_RECREATION_CONTRACTUAL_CONTROL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Contractual Control</em></p>
			<p>You have become a master at utilizing your receipts. The cost of materializing is halved, and creations you use with Contractual Control can be used a number of times equal to your proficiency bonus before they disappear.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>The cost of materialization is halved. Your creations are usable {{proficiency}} times.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Cursed Cannon -->
	<element name="Detonate" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DETONATE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Granite Blast</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_CANNON_GRANITE_BLAST</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Granite Blast</em></p>
			<p>You have realized a new way to utilize your massive output. You can now use your Granite Blast as a melee cursed energy attack. This cannot be used with Grape Shot.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Granite Blast can be used as a melee CE attack. This cannot be used with Grape Shot.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Canshot" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CANSHOT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Grape Shot</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_CANNON_GRAPE_SHOT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Grape Shot</em></p>
			<p>The ability to control your Granite Blasts has improved further. Once per turn on a hit with one Granite Blast, you can spend an additional 2 Cursed Energy, forcing all creatures within 5 feet of the target to make a Dexterity save, taking half the damage on a failed save as the attack splits on impact.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>Once per turn on a hit with one Granite Blast, you can spend an additional 2 CE, forcing all creatures within 5 feet of the target to make a Dexterity save, taking half the damage on a failed save.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Antimatter Bomb" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_ANTIMATTER_BOMB">
		<prerequisite>Must have Nuclear Shell</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_CANNON_NUCLEAR_SHELL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Nuclear Shell</em></p>
			<p>You have found a brand new and destructive pathway for your technique. When you use Nuclear Shell, you can instead spend 6 CE to change the area of effect to a 100-foot radius sphere surrounding yourself. On a failure, all creatures are knocked prone and stunned until the beginning of their next turn. All structures take maximum damage and non magical objects not worn or held are reduced to dust.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you use Nuclear Shell, you can instead spend 6 CE to change the area of effect to a 100-foot radius sphere surrounding yourself. On a failure, all creatures are knocked prone and stunned until the beginning of their next turn. All structures take maximum damage and non magical objects not worn or held are reduced to dust.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Cursed Corpse Creation -->
	<element name="Expert Maker" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EXPERT_MAKER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Corpse Creation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CORPSE_CREATION_CORPSE_CREATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Corpse Creation</em></p>
			<p>You have spent your life learning your technique and learned tips and tricks that help you master the process. You can create a cursed core or body for 1/3 of the cost or time.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can create a cursed core or body for 1/3 of the cost or time.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Soul Imbuement" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SOUL_IMBUEMENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Corpse Creation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CORPSE_CREATION_CORPSE_CREATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Corpse Creation</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to copy a creature's soul information into a Cursed Corpse. You can only have 1 soul imbued corpse at a time. This increases to 2 at 11th level and 3 at 18th level.</p>
			<p class="indent">It takes 3 long rests to imbue someone's soul information into the core. You must have the person readily available or have a good memory of the person to turn their physical information into soul information. Once a corpse has been created, it takes 2 weeks to develop before it becomes sentient. It gains the Autonomy mutation and can choose a Cursed Energy feat as if it were a player. A corpse with this core is sentient and mimics the behavior of the soul they are imbued with, but it does not gain its memories.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can have {{corpse:creation:soul:imbuement:max}} soul imbued corpse at a time. It takes 3 long rests to imbue someone's soul information into the core. You must have the person readily available or have a good memory of the person to turn their physical information into soul information. Once a corpse has been created, it takes 2 weeks to develop before it becomes sentient. It gains the Autonomy mutation and can choose a Cursed Energy feat as if it were a player. A corpse with this core is sentient and mimics the behavior of the soul they are imbued with, but it does not gain its memories.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="corpse:creation:soul:imbuement:max" value="1" bonus="soul imbuement" />
			<stat name="corpse:creation:soul:imbuement:max" value="2" bonus="soul imbuement" level="11" />
			<stat name="corpse:creation:soul:imbuement:max" value="3" bonus="soul imbuement" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Cursed Tactician" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CURSED_TACTICIAN">
		<prerequisite>Must have Corpse Tactics</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CORPSE_CREATION_CORPSE_TACTICS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Corpse Tactics</em></p>
			<p>When you use Corpse Tactics, you can spend CE up to your proficiency bonus to use an additional tactics option for each CE spent. You can choose the same tactics option as part of the same bonus action, but you cannot use the same tactics multiple times on the same cursed corpse.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use Corpse Tactics, you can spend up to {{proficiency}} CE to use an additional tactic per CE spent. You can choose the same tactics option, but cannot use the same tactics multiple times on the same cursed corpse.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Mutate Specialist" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MUTATE_SPECIALIST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Corpse Mutation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CORPSE_CREATION_CORPSE_MUTATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Corpse Mutation</em></p>
			<p>You have learned the process to purposely force mutations to occur. When you roll for a mutation, you can add your Cursed Energy modifier to the roll. If you succeed, you roll for an additional mutation for every number higher than 20. You cannot gain the same mutation more than once.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you roll for a mutation, you can add {{ce:modifier}} to the roll. If you succeed, you roll for an additional mutation for every number higher than 20. You cannot gain the same mutation more than once.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Cursed Speech -->
	<element name="Fighting Words" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FIGHTING_WORDS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Power of Words</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPEECH_POWER_OF_WORDS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Power of Words</em></p>
			<p>“Oh, them's fighting words.” You have found a way to make your words insulting. When using a word, you can force the enemy to make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failure, they have disadvantage on attack rolls against creatures other than you.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use a word, you can force a Wisdom save. On a failure, the target has disadvantage on attack rolls against creatures other than you.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Quick Tongue" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_QUICK_TONGUE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Interjection</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPEECH_INTERJECTION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Interjection</em></p>
			<p>Your versatility and training have increased the amount of words you have and your speed. You can choose one more word to be under the effect of Interjection.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Archetype Feature" name="Interjection" supports="Interjection" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Megaphone" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MEGAPHONE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Resounding Voice</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPEECH_RESOUNDING_VOICE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Resounding Voice</em></p>
			<p>You have found a way to increase your power using an outside tool. For 3 Cursed Energy you can create or imbue a megaphone for 1 minute that causes your words to affect a 60-foot cone. The megaphone has hit points equal to twice your CE score and damages the megaphone instead of your vocal chords when used in this way. When reduced to 0 hit points, the megaphone turns to dust.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, create a megaphone for 1 minute that makes your words affect a 60-foot cone. The megaphone has {{cursed:speech:megaphone:hp}} HP and takes damage instead of your vocal chords. It is destroyed at 0 HP.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="cursed:speech:megaphone:hp" value="cu:stat" />
			<stat name="cursed:speech:megaphone:hp" value="cu:stat" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Cursed Spirit Manipulation -->
	<element name="Curse Restoration" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CURSE_RESTORATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Curse Infused Spirits</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_CURSE_INFUSED_SPIRITS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Curse Infused Spirits</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to weaponize the affinity cursed spirits have for regeneration. Once per turn, as an action, bonus action, or reaction, you can spend up to your cursed energy modifier to restore 5 hit points per cursed energy spent to a cursed spirit you have summoned within 60 feet of you.</p>
			<p>At 11th level, this becomes 10 hit points per cursed energy spent.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action, Bonus Action, or Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>Once per turn, spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE to heal a summoned cursed spirit within 60 ft for 5 HP per CE .</description>
			<description level="11">Once per turn, spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE to heal a summoned cursed spirit within 60 ft for 10 HP per CE .</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Defensive Summoning" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DEFENSIVE_SUMMONING">
		<prerequisite>Must have Perfect Control</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_PERFECT_CONTROL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Perfect Control</em></p>
			<p>Your reaction speed and control over your cursed spirits has increased. As a reaction, for 5 Cursed Energy, you can summon a CR 5 or lower cursed spirit that takes as much of the triggering damage as it can. You take any remaining damage. If the spirit survives, it appears in an unoccupied space within 5 feet of you.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 CE, summon a CR 5 or lower cursed spirit that absorbs incoming damage. You take any remaining damage. If it survives, it appears within an unoccupied space within 5 ft of you.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Minimum: Uzumaki" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MINIMUM_UZUMAKI">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Uzumaki</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_CURSED_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_MAXIMUM_UZUMAKI</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Uzumaki</em></p>
			<p>Due to your extended studies, you have made a smaller version of Uzumaki that's more deadly and much harder to dodge. As a bonus action, you can spend two cursed spirits to create a miniature Uzumaki that fits in your hand. It can't be seen by the creature unless its passive Perception is 25 or higher, or the creature succeeds a Perception check. As an action or reaction for 5 Cursed Energy, you can release all the condensed energy from this Uzumaki at a target within 30 feet. Make a ranged cursed energy attack roll, on a hit the target takes Xd12 of necrotic damage(X being the combined CR of the 2 curses). Like Maximum Uzumaki, this ignores resistance and treats immunity like resistance. You have advantage on your attack roll if the target has not detected your Minimum Uzumaki.</p>
			<p class="indent">Similar to Maximum Uzumaki, you can obtain actions, bonus actions, reactions, or legendary actions tied to the absorbed technique.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>Spend 2 cursed spirits to create a miniature Uzumaki that can't be seen by creatures unless they have at least a 25 passive Perception or suceed on a Perception check. As an action or reaction for 5 CE, make a ranged CE attack at a target within 30 feet. On a hit they take Xd12 necrotic (X = combined CR of cursed spirits). This ignores resistance, treats immunity as resistance, and you have advantage if undetected. You can extract the features of cursed spirits used this way.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Dark Claw -->
	<element name="Close Combat Specialist" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CLOSE_COMBAT_SPECIALIST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Claw</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DARK_CLAW_CLAW</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Claw</em></p>
			<p>When you hit a creature with a claw attack while within 5 feet, you can attempt to grapple the creature as a bonus action. While grappling a creature, it takes your claw damage at the start of its turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>On a claw hit within 5 ft, you can attempt to grapple the target. Grappled creatures take your claw damage at the start of their turn.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Drill Claws" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DRILL_CLAWS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Claws Modifications</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DARK_CLAW_CLAWS_MODIFICATIONS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Claws Modifications</em></p>
			<p> You have learned to control the length of your claws. As a bonus action, you lengthen your claws and increase your melee reach with them by 5 ft for 1 minute or until you retract them as a bonus action. </p>
			<p class="indent"> Additionally, you learn to shoot out your claws as projectiles. Once per turn when you take the Attack action you can spend 1 CE to replace one of your attacks with a Drill Claw attack. You make a ranged Claw attack using your Strength, Dexterity, or Cursed Energy modifier against a creature within 30 ft. On a hit, this attack deals 4d8 piercing damage. This increases to 6d8 at 6th level, 8d8 at 11th level and 10d8 at 18th level. The range of this attack doubles at 6th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>Increase your melee range with your claws by 5 ft for 1 minute or until retracted as a bonus action. Once per turn when you take the Attack action you can spend 1 CE to replace one of your attacks with a ranged Claw attack using your Strength, Dexterity, or CE modifier against a creature within {{dark:claw:drill:claws:range}} ft. On a hit, this attack deals {{dark:claw:drill:claws:damage}}d8 piercing damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:damage" value="4" bonus="drill claws" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:damage" value="6" level="6" bonus="drill claws" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:damage" value="8" level="11" bonus="drill claws" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:damage" value="10" level="18" bonus="drill claws" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:range" value="30" bonus="drill claws" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:drill:claws:range" value="60" level="6" bonus="drill claws" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Cutting Edge" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CUTTING_EDGE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ultimate Claws</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DARK_CLAW_ULTIMATE_CLAWS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ultimate Claws</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to sharpen your claws with cursed energy. You gain a +1 bonus to critical range with your Claws and can reroll and 1s or 2s when rolling damage for your Claws. The bonus to critical range increases to +2 at 11th level and +3 at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your claws have a +{{dark:claw:cutting:edge:range}} to their critical range and can reroll 1s and 2s on damage rolls.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="dark:claw:cutting:edge:range" value="1" bonus="cutting edge" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:cutting:edge:range" value="2" level="11" bonus="cutting edge" />
			<stat name="dark:claw:cutting:edge:range" value="3" level="18" bonus="cutting edge" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Deadly Sentencing -->
	<element name="Tool Versatility" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TOOL_VERSATILITY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Judge's Gavel</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DEADLY_SENTENCING_JUDGES_GAVEL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Judge's Gavel</em></p>
			<p>Through a broadening of your understanding over your gavel. On top of your normal forms, you can turn your Gavel into any melee weapon. You also gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls using your Gavel. This increases to a +2 bonus at 6th level and +3 bonus at 11th level. The Executioner's Sword does not gain this bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your Gavel can become any melee weapon and gains a +{{deadly:sentencing:tool:versatility:bonus}} to attack and damage rolls. The Executioner's Sword does not gain this bonus.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="deadly:sentencing:tool:versatility:bonus" value="1" />
			<stat name="deadly:sentencing:tool:versatility:bonus" value="2" level="6" bonus="tool versatility" />
			<stat name="deadly:sentencing:tool:versatility:bonus" value="3" level="11" bonus="tool versatility" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Weight of Judgment" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WEIGHT_OF_JUDGMENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Deadly Sentencing</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DEADLY_SENTENCING_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_DEADLY_SENTENCING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Deadly Sentencing</em></p>
			<p>When you hit a creature with your Judge's Gavel, you can spend 2 CE to double the weapon's damage dice. The creature must also make a Strength saving throw or fall prone.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>On a hit with your Gavel for 2 CE, double the weapon's damage dice and force the target to succeed on a Strength save or fall prone.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Judgeman Release" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_JUDGEMAN_RELEASE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Gavel Improvements</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DEADLY_SENTENCING_GAVEL_IMPROVEMENTS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Gavel Improvements</em></p>
			<p>Your attunement with Deadly Sentencing has allowed you to summon Judgeman outside the domain. As a bonus action for 5 Cursed Energy, you summon Judgeman for 1 minute. Every time your opponent attacks you, they are penalized for assault and the opponent gains a -1 penalty to attack rolls and saving throws. If a creature targets you with a cursed technique that is not an attack roll, they gain a -1 penalty to their CE save DC. These penalties last until Judgeman disappears.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 CE, for 1 minute every time a opponent attacks you they gain a -1 penalty to attack rolls and saving throws. If a creature targets you with a cursed technique that is not an attack roll, they gain a -1 penalty to their CE save DC. These penalties last for the duration.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Disaster Flames -->
	<element name="Pyrokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PYROKINESIS1">
		<prerequisite>Must have Flames of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_FLAMES_FLAMES_OF_DISASTER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Flames of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your flames. You gain the one of the following (This feat can be taken more than once):</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Resistance to Fire Damage and when you roll damage for a technique that deals fire damage, you can reroll any 1s, but must take the new result, even if the new roll is a 1.</li>
				<li>Two spells below 5th level dealing fire damage. The ce cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Pyrokinesis" supports="Pyrokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Pyrokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PYROKINESIS2">
		<prerequisite>Must have Flames of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_PYROKINESIS1</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Flames of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your flames. You gain the one of the following (This feat can be taken more than once):</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Resistance to Fire Damage and when you roll damage for a technique that deals fire damage, you can reroll any 1s, but must take the new result, even if the new roll is a 1.</li>
				<li>Two spells below 5th level dealing fire damage. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Pyrokinesis" supports="Pyrokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Fire Affinity" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_FLAMES_FIRE_AFFINITY">
		<supports>Pyrokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Resistance to Fire Damage and when you roll damage for a technique that deals fire damage, you can reroll any 1s, but must take the new result, even if the new roll is a 1.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you roll damage for a technique that deals fire damage, you can reroll any 1s, but must take the new result.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Condition" id="ID_INTERNAL_CONDITION_DAMAGE_RESISTANCE_FIRE" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Spells" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_FLAMES_SPELLS">
		<supports>Pyrokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Two spells below 5th level dealing fire damage. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can cast the selected spells for CE equal to the spell's level.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<select type="Spell" name="4th Level or Below Fire Spells (Pyrokinesis)" supports="ID_PHB_SPELL_BURNING_HANDS|ID_PHB_SPELL_FIRE_SHIELD|ID_PHB_SPELL_FIREBALL|ID_PHB_SPELL_FLAME_BLADE|ID_PHB_SPELL_FLAMING_SPHERE|ID_PHB_SPELL_HELLISH_REBUKE|ID_PHB_SPELL_SCORCHING_RAY|ID_PHB_SPELL_SEARING_SMITE|ID_PHB_SPELL_WALL_OF_FIRE|ID_XGTE_SPELL_AGANAZZARS_SCORCHER|ID_XGTE_SPELL_FLAME_ARROWS|ID_XGTE_SPELL_MELFS_MINUTE_METEORS" number="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Shooting Star" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHOOTING_STAR">
		<prerequisite>Must have Erupting Volcanoes</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_FLAMES_ERUPTING_VOLCANOES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Erupting Volcanoes</em></p>
			<p>Through focus and thorough planning, you have gained further ideas. As a bonus action, you can gain a 60 foot hover speed for as many rounds as Cursed Energy spent.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>Spend CE to gain a 60 ft hover speed for that many rounds.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Hellscape" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_HELLSCAPE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Meteor</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_FLAMES_MAXIMUM_METEOR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Meteor</em></p>
			<p>Your presence can now be felt, all around. As an action for 10 Cursed Energy, you can cause all non magical objects and structures of your choice in a 100 foot radius to melt. As an action you can control where the lava flows or control it directly to make two cursed energy attacks against a creature within range, dealing 10d8 fire damage on a hit. Each creature that enters the lava or starts their turn touching the lava must make a Constitution saving throw, taking 8d8 fire damage on a failed save or half as much on a success.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, all non magical objects and structures of your choice in a 100 foot radius melt. As an action you can control the lava to make two CE attacks against a creature within range, dealing 10d8 fire damage on a hit. Each creature that enters the lava or starts their turn touching the lava must make a Constitution saving throw, taking 8d8 fire damage on a failed save or half as much on a success.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Disaster Tides -->
	<element name="Hydrokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_HYDROKINESIS1">
		<prerequisite>Must have Tides of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_TIDES_TIDES_OF_DISASTER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Tides of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your water. You gain the one of the following (You can select this feat multiple times):</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Piercing Water:</strong> You make a small water beam made to pierce through enemies. As an action for 2 CE, you make a cursed energy attack against a creature within 30 ft. On a hit, they take 2d10 cold damage + 2d6 piercing damage and are forced to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they are knocked prone and will receive the damage rolled one additional time as a vital organ is hit. On a success, they don't take additional damage and are not prone.</li>
				<li>Two water spells below 5th level. The CE cost equals the spell's level in Cursed Energy.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Hydrokinesis" supports="Hydrokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Hydrokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_HYDROKINESIS2">
		<prerequisite>Must have Tides of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_HYDROKINESIS1</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Tides of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your water. You gain the one of the following (You can select this feat multiple times):</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Piercing Water:</strong> You make a small water beam made to pierce through enemies. As an action for 2 CE, you make a cursed energy attack against a creature within 30 ft. On a hit, they take 2d10 cold damage + 2d6 piercing damage and are forced to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they are knocked prone and will receive the damage rolled one additional time as a vital organ is hit. On a success, they don't take additional damage and are not prone.</li>
				<li>Two water spells below 5th level. The CE cost equals the spell's level in Cursed Energy.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Hydrokinesis" supports="Hydrokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Piercing Water" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_TIDES_PIERCING_WATER">
		<supports>Hydrokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You make a small water beam made to pierce through enemies. As an action for 2 CE, you make a cursed energy attack against a creature within 30 ft. On a hit, they take 2d10 cold damage + 2d6 piercing damage and are forced to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they are knocked prone and will receive the damage rolled one additional time as a vital organ is hit. On a success, they don't take additional damage and are not prone.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, make a cursed energy attack against a creature within 30 ft. On a hit, they take 2d10 cold damage + 2d6 piercing damage and are forced to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they are knocked prone and will receive the damage rolled one additional time. On a success, they don't take additional damage and are not prone.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Spells" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_TIDES_SPELLS">
		<supports>Hydrokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Two water spells below 5th level. The CE cost equals the spell's level in Cursed Energy.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can cast the selected spells for CE equal to the spell's level.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<select type="Spell" name="4th Level or Lower Water Spells (Hydrokinesis)" supports="ID_PHB_SPELL_ARMOR_OF_AGATHYS|ID_PHB_SPELL_CONTROL_WATER|ID_PHB_SPELL_CREATE_FOOD_AND_WATER|ID_PHB_SPELL_CREATE_OR_DESTROY_WATER|ID_PHB_SPELL_ICE_STORM|ID_PHB_SPELL_SLEET_STORM|ID_PHB_SPELL_WATER_BREATHING|ID_PHB_SPELL_WATER_WALK|ID_XGTE_SPELL_ICE_KNIFE|ID_XGTE_SPELL_TIDAL_WAVE|ID_XGTE_SPELL_WALL_OF_WATER|ID_XGTE_SPELL_WATERY_SPHERE|ID_XGTE_SPELL_SNILLOCS_SNOWBALL_SWARM" number="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Shoal" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHOAL">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Horizon of Captivating Skhanda</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_TIDES_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_HORIZON_OF_CAPTIVATING_SKHANDA</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Horizon of Captivating Skhanda</em></p>
			<p>You have increased your technique's potential. You can now use Death Swarm outside your domain without the sure hit effect. You can have a number of shikigami equal to your Cursed Energy modifier when used in this way. The number of shikigami increases by your CE modifier at 6th level (2x), 11th level (3x), and 18th level (4x).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can use Death Swarm outside your domain without the sure hit. You can have up to {{disaster:tides:shoal:max}} shikigami when used this way.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="disaster:tides:shoal:max" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="disaster:tides:shoal:max" value="ce:modifier" level="6" />
			<stat name="disaster:tides:shoal:max" value="ce:modifier" level="11" />
			<stat name="disaster:tides:shoal:max" value="ce:modifier" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Typhoon" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TYPHOON">
		<prerequisite>Must have Water Defensive Ring</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_TIDES_WATER_DEFENSIVE_RING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Water Defensive Ring</em></p>
			<p>The scale and power of the water ring surrounding you has increased. For an extra 4 cursed energy, it also creates a 20 ft radius sphere of whirling storm centered on you. Each creature other than you in the sphere when it appears or that ends its turn there must succeed on a Strength saving throw or take 2d6 bludgeoning damage. The sphere's space is difficult terrain.</p>
			<p class="indent">Until the technique ends, you can use a bonus action to cause a bolt of lightning to leap from you toward a creature within 60 feet, making a cursed energy attack. You have advantage on the attack if the target is in the sphere. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 lightning damage. Creatures within 30 feet of the sphere have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks to hear.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For an extra 4 CE, Water Defensive Ring also creates a 20 ft radius sphere centered on you. Each other creature in the sphere when it appears or that ends its turn there must succeed on a Strength saving throw or take 2d6 bludgeoning damage. The sphere's space is difficult terrain. Until the technique ends, you can use a bonus action to make a CE attack at a creature within 60 feet. You have advantage on the attack if the target is in the sphere. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 lightning damage. Creatures within 30 feet of the sphere have disadvantage on Perception checks to hear.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Disaster Verdure -->
	<element name="Chlorokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CHLOROKINESIS1">
		<prerequisite>Must have Forest of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERDURE_FORESTS_OF_DISASTER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Forest of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your roots. You gain the one of the following (You can select this feat multiple times):</p>
			<ul>
				<li>You can transform your root wall into any of the other forms as a bonus action.</li>
				<li>Two spells below 5th level dealing with nature. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Chlorokinesis" supports="Chlorokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Chlorokinesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CHLOROKINESIS2">
		<prerequisite>Must have Forest of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_CHLOROKINESIS1</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Forest of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>Through training and understanding, you have found new applications to your roots. You gain the one of the following (You can select this feat multiple times):</p>
			<ul>
				<li>You can transform your root wall into any of the other forms as a bonus action.</li>
				<li>Two spells below 5th level dealing with nature. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Chlorokinesis" supports="Chlorokinesis" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Chlorokinesis Transformation" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERDURE_CHLOROKINESIS_TRANSFORMATION">
		<supports>Chlorokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You can transform your root wall into any of the other forms as a bonus action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>Transform your root wall into any of the other forms</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Spells" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERDURE_SPELLS">
		<supports>Chlorokinesis</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Two spells below 5th level dealing with nature. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can cast the selected spells for CE equal to the spell's level.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<select type="Spell" name="4th Level or Lower Nature Spells (Chlorokinesis)" supports="ID_PHB_SPELL_LOCATE_ANIMALS_OR_PLANTS|ID_PHB_SPELL_ENTANGLE|ID_PHB_SPELL_BARKSKIN|ID_PHB_SPELL_PLANT_GROWTH|ID_PHB_SPELL_SPEAK_WITH_ANIMALS|ID_PHB_SPELL_GOODBERRY|ID_PHB_SPELL_DETECT_POISON_AND_DISEASE|ID_PHB_SPELL_SPIKE_GROWTH|ID_PHB_SPELL_PROTECTION_FROM_POISON|ID_PHB_SPELL_SPEAK_WITH_PLANTS|ID_PHB_SPELL_GRASPING_VINE" number="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Bouquet" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BOUQUET">
		<prerequisite>Must have Flower Field</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERDURE_FLOWER_FIELD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Flower Field</em></p>
			<p>You have found a way to do more with less. As an action, for 3 Cursed Energy you can cause the effects of Flower Field on a single creature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, apply Flower Field effects to a single target.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Sapping Roots" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SAPPING_ROOTS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Buds</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERDURE_CURSED_BUDS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Buds</em></p>
			<p>Your power has increased and been honed. As an action, for 5 Cursed Energy you give yourself the ability to drain Cursed Energy for 1 minute. On a hit with a melee attack or if you damage a creature with your Innate Technique, they lose 1 cursed energy which you gain.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 CE, for 1 minute on a hit with a melee attack or if you damage a creature with your Innate Technique, they lose 1 cursed energy which you gain.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Disaster Vermin -->
	<element name="Reinforced Vermin" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_REINFORCED_VERMIN">
		<prerequisite>Must have Vermin of Disaster</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_VERMIN_OF_DISASTER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Vermin of Disaster</em></p>
			<p>As part of the bonus action you take to summon or command your Insect Swarms, you can spend 2 cursed energy to reinforce one of your Insect Swarms with cursed energy for 1 minute. While reinforced, their size category increases by one and they deal an additional 2 damage dice on a successful Bites attack (only +1 if bloodied). If you use multiple Reinforced Insect Swarms to form a Vermin Swarm, it only gains these benefits once.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>As part of the bonus action you take to summon or command your Insect Swarms, you can spend 2 CE to give one Insect Swarm reinforcement for 1 minute. While reinforced, their size category increases by one and they deal an additional 2 damage dice on a successful Bites attack (only +1 if bloodied). If you use multiple Reinforced Insect Swarms to form a Vermin Swarm, it only gains these benefits once.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Vermin Techniques" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_VERMIN_TECHNIQUES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Almighty Swarm</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_ALMIGHTY_SWARM</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Almighty Swarm</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to better control the combined actions of your Vermin Swarms, allowing you to learn the following ways to use your Swarms:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Insect Cloak.</strong> While you are occupying the same space as one of your Vermin Swarms, you can treat the Swarm's hit points as temporary hit points for yourself.</li>
				<li><strong>Grasping Hand.</strong> You can spend 3 CE to replace one of your attacks on your turn with a grapple check through one of your Insect Swarms against a creature within 5 ft of the swarm. Instead of an Athletics check, you make a Cursed Energy (Arcana) check. The grapple gains a +1 bonus and +5 ft of range per size category above Medium the swarm is. On a success, the creature is grappled and can be pulled into the Insect Swarm.</li>
				<li><strong>Transport Via Bugs.</strong> As an action for 6 CE, you form a link between one Large or larger Vermin Swarm within 10 ft and connect it to another Large or larger Vermin Swarm at any distance. Before the end of your turn, you can spend 5 ft of movement to walk into the space of the Insect Swarm within 5 ft, reappearing within 5 ft of the destination Insect Swarm.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_INSECT_CLOAK" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_GRASPING_HAND" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_TRANSPORT_VIA_BUGS" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Insect Cloak" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_INSECT_CLOAK">
		<supports>Vermin Techniques</supports>
		<description>
			<p>While you are occupying the same space as one of your Vermin Swarms, you can treat the Swarm's hit points as temporary hit points for yourself.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While you are occupying the same space as one of your Vermin Swarms, you can treat the Swarm's hit points as temporary hit points for yourself.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Grasping Hand" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_GRASPING_HAND">
		<supports>Vermin Techniques</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You can spend 3 CE to replace one of your attacks on your turn with a grapple check through one of your Insect Swarms against a creature within 5 ft of the swarm. Instead of an Athletics check, you make a Cursed Energy (Arcana) check. The grapple gains a +1 bonus and +5 ft of range per size category above Medium the swarm is. On a success, the creature is grappled and can be pulled into the Insect Swarm.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, replace one attack with a grapple check through one of your Insect Swarms against a creature within 5 ft of the swarm. Instead of an Athletics check, make a CE Arcana check. The grapple gains a +1 bonus and +5 ft of range per size category above Medium the swarm is. On a success, the creature is grappled and can be pulled into the Insect Swarm.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Transport via Bugs" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_TRANSPORT_VIA_BUGS">
		<supports>Vermin Techniques</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You can use your Insect Swarms to transport you and your allies. As a bonus action, you can command a swarm to carry you or another creature within 5 ft of the swarm. The swarm can move up to its speed while carrying the load.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>Command an Insect Swarm to carry you or another creature within 5 ft of the swarm. The swarm can move up to its speed while carrying the load.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Festering Life Sword" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FESTERING_LIFE_SWORD">
		<prerequisite>Must have Parthenogenesis</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DISASTER_VERMIN_PARTHENOGENESIS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Parthenogenesis</em></p>
			<p>As a bonus action for 6 CE, you transform a weapon you are holding. It loses all previous benefits and becomes the Special Grade Cursed Tool: Festering Life Sword. You can only have one weapon transformed this way at a time and this tool disappears when you finish a long rest or die.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 6 CE, transform a weapon you are holding into a Festering Life Sword. It loses all previous benefits. You can only have one weapon transformed this way at a time and this tool disappears when you finish a long rest or die.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Divergent Fist -->
	<element name="Black Belt" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLACK_BELT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Martial Prowess</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_MARTIAL_PROWESS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Martial Prowess</em></p>
			<p> Through much training, you gain the following martial options:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Takedown.</strong> After a melee hit, grapple or shove as a bonus action.</li>
				<li><strong>Judo Throw.</strong> On hit vs grappled target: Strength save or prone; fail by 5+ = stunned.</li>
				<li><strong>Flying Drop Kick.</strong> Action: jump and make an unarmed attack, dealing damage and pushing 30 ft.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can use Takedown, Judo Throw, and Flying Drop Kick as Martial Prowess options.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_TAKEDOWN" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_JUDO_THROW" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_FLYING_DROP_KICK" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Takedown" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_TAKEDOWN">
		<description>
			<p>Immediately after you hit a creature with a melee attack on your turn, you can try to grapple or shove the target as a bonus action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Immediately after you hit a creature with a melee attack on your turn, you can try to grapple or shove the target as a bonus action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Judo Throw" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_JUDO_THROW">
		<description>
			<p>When you hit a grappled creature with a melee attack, you can grab the target and flip them on their back. If the target is Huge or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock them prone, and if they fail it by 5 or more they are stunned until the end of their next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you hit a grappled creature with a melee attack, you can force them to make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock them prone, and if they fail it by 5 or more they are stunned until the end of their next turn.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Flying Drop Kick" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_FLYING_DROP_KICK">
		<description>
			<p>You can use an action to jump up and land a Flying Drop Kick. You target a creature within your jump distance with an unarmed attack (Calculator here). The target takes your unarmed damage, and is pushed back 30ft.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Perform a unarmed attack against a creature within your jump distance. They are pushed back 30ft.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Opportunistic Blow" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_OPPORTUNISTIC_BLOW">
		<prerequisite>Must have Extreme Divergent Flow</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_EXTREME_DIVERGENT_FLOW</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Extreme Divergent Flow</em></p>
			<p>You take full advantage of the unpredictability of your attacks. After a Divergent Flow is landed, you can force the enemy to make a Cursed Energy check against your DC. On a failure, you notice their distraction and can use your reaction to make an attack against them at advantage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>After a Divergent Flow is landed, you can force the enemy to make a Cursed Energy check against your DC. On a failure, you can use your reaction to make an attack against them at advantage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Soul Punch" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SOUL_PUNCH">
		<prerequisite>Must have Chosen by the Sparks</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_DIVERGENT_FIST_CHOSEN_BY_THE_SPARKS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Chosen by the Sparks</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered your ability to target the soul. Before you make an unarmed strike, you can choose to spend 5 CE to cause any unarmed strikes you make on your turn to target the soul of a creature you attack. These attacks' damage reduces the target's maximum hit point and cannot be reduced or healed with Cursed Techniques or Reverse Cursed Technique as it targets the soul instead of the body. On a hit, the creature's output drops by 1, causing them to be able to spend 1 less cursed energy for cursed techniques. You can reduce a creature's output up to your Cursed Energy modifier. This effect lasts until the target takes a short or long rest. A creature whose output has been reduced cannot use maximum output techniques.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>Before you make an unarmed strike, you can choose to spend 5 CE to cause any unarmed strikes you make on your turn to target the soul of a creature. Your attacks reduce the target's maximum hit points and cannot be healed with Cursed Techniques or Reverse Cursed Technique and reduce the amount of CE they can spend for cursed techniques by 1. You can reduce a creature's output up to {{ce:modifier}}. This effect lasts until the target takes a short or long rest. A creature whose output has been reduced cannot use maximum output techniques.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Earth Manipulation -->
	<element name="Density Manipulation" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DENSITY_MANIPULATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Excavation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EARTH_MANIPULATION_EXCAVATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Excavation</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to increase the density of your stone creations. The amount of hit points each cube created by your Excavation now equals 10 times your CE modifier. Stone constructs created by your other Innate Technique features gain an additional 10 hit points.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:excavation:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:excavation:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:excavation:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:excavation:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:excavation:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:wallofstone:hitpoints" value="10" />
			<stat name="earth:manipulation:stonearms:hp" value="10" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Rock Burst" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ROCK_BURST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Sculpted Earth</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EARTH_MANIPULATION_SCULPTED_EARTH</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Sculpted Earth</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction, you can cause one of your stone constructs within 60 feet of you to explode. Any creature within 5 feet must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take 1d12 bludgeoning damage and are knocked prone. You can spend CE up to half your proficiency bonus (rounded down) as part of this reaction to heighten the explosion and deal an additional 1d12 bludgeoning damage per CE and cause creatures in range to take half as much damage on a success.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>Cause one of your stone constructs within 60 feet of you to explode. Any creature within 5 feet must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take 1d12 bludgeoning damage and are knocked prone. You can spend up to {{proficiency:half}} CE to heighten the explosion and deal an additional 1d12 bludgeoning damage per CE and cause creatures in range to take half as much damage on a success.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Arms of the Giant" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ARMS_OF_THE_GIANT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Stone Arms</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EARTH_MANIPULATION_STONE_ARMS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Stone Arms</em></p>
			<p>You are no longer required to maintain concentration to maintain your Stone Arms. Additionally, while spending 1 CE each turn to maintain your hands, you are able to control your Stone Arms as if casting the spell Bigby's Hand. A creature that gains the restrained condition from your Stone Arms has their movement speed halved for 1 minute or until they regain hit points.</p>
			<div class="reference">
				<div element="ID_PHB_SPELL_BIGBYS_HAND" />
			</div>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your Stone Arms do not need concentration. While maintaining your hands, you are able to control your Stone Arms as if casting the spell Bigby's Hand. A creature that gains the restrained condition from your Stone Arms has their movement speed halved for 1 minute or until they regain hit points.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_BIGBYS_HAND" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Explosive Flesh -->
	<element name="Reduced Harm" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_REDUCED_HARM">
		<prerequisite>Must have Faster Throws</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EXPLOSIVE_FLESH_FASTER_THROWS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Faster Throws</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to minimize the damage you take when using your technique. You decrease the hit point loss from using any part of your body as an explosive by an amount equal to your Constitution modifier (minimum 1 hit point).</p>
			<p class="indent">At 6th level, this reduction increases to an amount equal to twice your Constitution modifier plus your level (minimum 1 hit point).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Decrease the hp loss from using body parts by {{explosive:flesh:reduced:harm}} to a minimum of 1.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="explosive:flesh:reduced:harm" value="constitution:modifier" />
			<stat name="explosive:flesh:reduced:harm" value="constitution:modifier" level="6" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Elemental Bomb" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ELEMENTAL_BOMB">
		<prerequisite>Must have Guerilla Tactics</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EXPLOSIVE_FLESH_GUERILLA_TACTICS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Guerilla Tactics</em></p>
			<p>You have learned how to create different types of explosions, making them create different effects. You can spend additional cursed energy equal to the energy spent in using the bomb to make them an elemental bomb. The elemental bomb will deal additional dice of fire, cold or lightning damage, equal to the original bombs' damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>You can spend additional CE equal to the energy spent in using a explosive to make it do additional dice of fire, cold, or lightning damage equal to the original bombs' damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Bites the Dust" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BITES_THE_DUST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Stronger Explosions</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_EXPLOSIVE_FLESH_STRONGER_EXPLOSIONS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Stronger Explosions</em></p>
			<p>Your explosive prowess has reached new heights, allowing you to trigger massive blasts from your removed body parts. As an action, you can spend cursed energy equal to the body part to trigger a delayed explosion. Choose a body part you have removed within 30 ft. It detonates at the end of your next turn, forcing all creatures within 20 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw at disadvantage. On a failure, they take Xd12 force damage and are knocked prone. On a success, they take half damage and are not knocked prone. You can spend additional cursed energy up to half your proficiency bonus (rounded up) to increase the damage by an additional Xd12 for every cursed energy spent. The X is your Cursed Energy modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>You can spend CE equal to a body part you have removed within 30 ft to detonate it at the end of your next turn, forcing all creatures within 20 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw at disadvantage. On a failure, they take {{ce:modifier}}d12 force damage and are knocked prone. On a success, they take half damage and are not knocked prone. You can spend up to {{proficiency:half:up}} additional CE up to increase the damage by an additional {{ce:modifier}}d12 for every cursed energy spent.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Fate -->
	<element name="Destined One" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DESTINED_ONE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Fate Manipulation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FATE_FATE_MANIPULATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Fate Manipulation</em></p>
			<p>You or the DM chooses one creature you touch as your Destined One. You can always tell where your Destined One is as the thread of Fate always guides your hand. While within 30 ft of your Destined One, you have advantage on saving throws against being charmed or frightened. Additionally, once per round you can add your proficiency bonus to your AC against an attack roll made against you or to a saving throw you make, potentially changing the outcome. You cannot change the creature chosen as your Destined One unless they die.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You or the DM chooses one creature you touch as your Destined One. You can always tell where your Destined One is. While within 30 ft of your Destined One, you have advantage on saving throws against being charmed or frightened. Once per round you can add {{proficiency}} to your AC against an attack roll made against you or to a saving throw you make. You cannot change the creature chosen as your Destined One unless they die.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Web of Fate" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WEB_OF_FATE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Eyes of Fate</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FATE_CURSED_EYES_OF_FATE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Eyes of Fate</em></p>
			<p>When you cast a Fate onto targets, you can instead target a number of creatures equal to your proficiency bonus that are within range. If the Fate requires Touch, you must touch all targets of the technique.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you cast a Fate onto targets, you can instead target {{proficiency}} creatures that are within range. If the Fate requires Touch, you must touch all targets of the technique.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Shears of Three Fates" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SHEARS_OF_THREE_FATES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Road of Karma</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_FATE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_ROAD_OF_KARMA</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Road of Karma</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 15 cursed energy, you form a scissor with your fingers and snip one of the threads of fate of a creature you can see within 5 ft of you. At the start of each of the target's turns, they must make a Death save. This roll cannot have advantage or disadvantage and the target gains 1 level of exhaustion for every failed death save. If the target fails 3 death saves, they fall to 0 hit points and die. They are unable to be revived by cursed techniques. If the target succeeds 3 death saves or you are reduced to 0 hit points or die, the technique ends and the target becomes immune to this technique for 3 days.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 15 CE, force a creature within 5 ft of you that you can see to start making Death saves. This roll cannot have advantage or disadvantage and the target gains 1 level of exhaustion for every failed death save. If the target fails 3 death saves, they fall to 0 hit points and die. They are unable to be revived by cursed techniques. If the target succeeds 3 death saves or you are reduced to 0 hit points or die, the technique ends and the target becomes immune to this technique for 3 days.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- G Warstaff -->
	<element name="Greater Foresight" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_GREATER_FORESIGHT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Predictable Strikes</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Predictable Strikes</em></p>
			<p>Your foresight ability has reached even greater potential, reaching the point some consider enlightened. Whenever you have advantage because of your technique, you can roll 3 dice instead of 2 and keep the highest roll. Also, whenever a creature has disadvantage on attack rolls against you because of your technique, they roll 3 dice instead of 2 and keep the lowest roll.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Whenever you have advantage because of your technique, you can roll 3 dice instead of 2 and keep the highest roll. Also, whenever a creature has disadvantage on attack rolls against you because of your technique, they roll 3 dice instead of 2 and keep the lowest roll.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="GG True Warstaff" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_GG_TRUE_WARSTAFF">
		<prerequisite>Must have Precognition</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Precognition</em></p>
			<p>You have created a more powerful version of your G Warstaff, being a true weapon of destruction. As a bonus action while you have G Warstaff active, you can spend 4 cursed energy to evolve it into its true form, GG True Warstaff. It gains the following benefits for 1 minute:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>It deals one additional damage dice</li>
				<li>Its reach is 15ft instead of 10ft</li>
				<li>When you score a critical hit against a creature, you gain 2 seconds instead of 1</li>
				<li>It gains a +1 to critical range</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 4 CE while your Warstaff is active, it deals one additional damage dice, its reach is 15ft, when you score a critical hit you gain 2 seconds instead of 1, and it gains a +1 to critical range.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Omniscient Reader's Viewpoint" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_OMNISCIENT_READERS_VIEWPOINT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Storyboard Dominion</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Storyboard Dominion</em></p>
			<p>You have gained the ability to not only see, but also manipulate the contents of your manga panel. At the beginning of your turn, you can choose a creature that you can see that is marked by 6 seconds and roll a d20. Record the roll. As a reaction, you can replace one roll that creature makes with the result of that roll. At the beginning of your turn, you lose any unused rolls.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>At the beginning of your turn, you can choose a creature that you can see that is marked by 6 seconds and roll a d20. Record the roll. As a reaction, you can replace one roll that creature makes with the result of that roll. At the beginning of your turn, you lose any unused rolls.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Hair Manipulation -->

	<element name="Scorpion Tactics" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SCORPION_TACTICS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Scorpion Hair</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Scorpion Hair</em></p>
			<p>You have trained with your hair and unlocked the following maneuvers:</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Barbed Defense.</strong> As a reaction to being targeted by an attack, you can make a Scorpion Hair attack against the attacker if they are within range.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Hair Wrapping.</strong> On a hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can choose to deal no damage and instead grapple the creature. You can use your Cursed Energy modifier to make grapple checks with your hair.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Split Ends.</strong> Once per turn, when you hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can add your Cursed Energy modifier to the damage roll.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_BARBED_DEFENSE" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_HAIR_WRAPPING" />
			<grant type="Feat Feature" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_SPLIT_ENDS" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Barbed Defense" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_BARBED_DEFENSE">
		<description>
			<p>As a reaction to being targeted by an attack, you can make a Scorpion Hair attack against the attacker if they are within range.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction">
			<description>As a reaction to being targeted by an attack, you can make a Scorpion Hair attack against the attacker if they are within range.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Hair Wrapping" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_HAIR_WRAPPING">
		<description>
			<p>On a hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can choose to deal no damage and instead grapple the creature. You can use your Cursed Energy modifier to make grapple checks with your hair.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>On a hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can choose to deal no damage and instead grapple the creature. You can use your CE modifier to make grapple checks with your hair.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Split Ends" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_TACTICS_SPLIT_ENDS">
		<description>
			<p>Once per turn, when you hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can add your Cursed Energy modifier to the damage roll.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Once per turn, when you hit with your Scorpion Hair, you can add {{ce:modifier}} to the damage roll.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Mega-Drill" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MEGA_DRILL">
		<prerequisite>Must have Drill Hair</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Drill Hair</em></p>
			<p>You can now use more cursed energy to imbue one Mega-drill. As an action for 4 cursed energy, you can shoot this Mega-drill in a 5 ft wide, 80 ft long line. Creatures in this line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, it deals 6d10 piercing damage. On a success, they take half the damage. This technique deals maximum damage to objects and structures and ignores half and three quarters cover. The damage of this technique increases to 8d10 at 6th level and becomes 10d10 at 11th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 4 CE, creatures in a 5 ft wide, 80 ft long line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they take {{hair:manipulation:mega:drill:damage}}d10 piercing damage. On a success, they take half the damage. This technique deals maximum damage to objects and structures and ignores half and three quarters cover.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:mega:drill:damage" value="6" bonus="mega drill" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:mega:drill:damage" value="8" bonus="mega drill" level="6" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:mega:drill:damage" value="10" bonus="mega drill" level="11" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Air Bomber" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_AIR_BOMBER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Aircraft Hair</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Aircraft Hair</em></p>
			<p>You have learned the following destructive ways to amplify your Aircraft Hair forms:</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Copter Frenzy.</strong> As an action for 5 CE, you force all creatures within 15 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save they take your Helicopter Hair damage. On a successful save, they take half as much.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Jet Crash.</strong> The damage a creature takes from impacting a solid surface from your crash increases to 1d6 per 10 ft traveled in a straight line before hitting the. This becomes 1d8 at 11th level and 1d10 at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>If using Helicopter Hair, as an action for 5 CE force all creatures within 15 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw taking your Helicopter Hair damage on a fail and half as much on a save. If using Jet Hair, the damage a creature takes from impacting a solid surface from your crash increases to 1d{{hair:manipulation:air:bomber:damage}}.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:air:bomber:damage" value="6" bonus="jet crash" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:air:bomber:damage" value="8" bonus="jet crash" level="11" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:air:bomber:damage" value="10" bonus="jet crash" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Heart Catch -->
	<element name="Lover's Embrace" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_LOVERS_EMBRACE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Hands of Love</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HEART_CATCH_HANDS_OF_LOVE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Hands of Love</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered the basic use of your love hands. Whenever you Shove a creature, they are instead pushed 10 feet. When creatures are grappled or restrained, they take a d6 bludgeoning damage at the start of their turn. Structures also take maximum damage from your Love Hands.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Whenever you Shove a creature, they are instead pushed 10 feet. When creatures are grappled or restrained, they take a d6 bludgeoning damage at the start of their turn. Structures also take maximum damage from your Love Hands.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Handy Dandy" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_HANDY_DANDY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Hand Shield</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HEART_CATCH_HAND_SHIELD</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Hand Shield</em></p>
			<p>You use your Love Hands in new and innovative ways. As an action, you can make your Hands into a solid platform. This can be used for traversing, or area control and gives you and another creature that is large or smaller a hover speed of 15 ft while on it.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Make your Hands into a solid platform. This gives you and another creature that is large or smaller a hover speed of 15 ft while on it.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Love at First Sight" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_LOVE_AT_FIRST_SIGHT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cutie Honey</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HEART_CATCH_CUTIE_HONEY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cutie Honey</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 8 CE, you can choose to instantly put a creature you can see under the effects of Cutie Honey without needing to restrain them.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 8 CE, instantly put a creature you can see under the effects of Cutie Honey without needing to restrain them.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Ice Formation -->
	<element name="Iceshape" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ICESHAPE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ice Creation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ICE_FORMATION_ICE_CREATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ice Creation</em></p>
			<p>You have gained the ability to further shape your ice into a weapon. As an action for 1 Cursed Energy you can make a weapon made of ice or transform ice into a weapon for 1 minute. Once per turn, you can deal additional cold damage equal to your CE modifier on an attack made with that weapon.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 1 CE, you can make a ice weaponn for 1 minute. Once per turn, you can deal {{ce:modifier}} additional cold damage on an attack made with that weapon.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Frostbite" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FROSTBITE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Frost Calm</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ICE_FORMATION_FROST_CALM</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Frost Calm</em></p>
			<p>The cold of your ice has increased exponentially. While restrained by your ice, your opponent gains an additional temporary level of exhaustion and a -2 to attack rolls and ability checks.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While restrained by your ice, your opponent gains an additional temporary level of exhaustion and a -2 to attack rolls and ability checks.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Shatter" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SHATTER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ice Fall</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ICE_FORMATION_ICE_FALL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ice Fall</em></p>
			<p>You now freeze through flesh and muscle. As an action while within 5 ft of a creature that is restrained by your ice, you can break off a limb that is not the head or torso (Using the limb damage table). The creature is then no longer restrained.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>While within 5 ft of a creature that is restrained by your ice, you can break off a limb that is not the head or torso (Using the limb damage table). The creature is then no longer restrained.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Idle Transfiguration -->
	<element name="Transfiguration Adept" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TRANSFIGURATION_ADEPT1">
		<prerequisite>Must have Transfiguration</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Transfiguration</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered your observation of the soul and learned grotesque molds to shape them into. You gain the two of the following ways to use transfigured humans (this feat can be repeated):</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Remote Transfiguration.</strong> When using Transfiguration, you can instead imprint a small, latent amount  of cursed energy upon their souls, allowing you to transfigure them from large distances (only one touch per creature).</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Wall of Flesh.</strong> As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus to form a flat panel of human flesh up to 5 ft long and wide per human used in an unoccupied space within 5 ft. The wall's AC equals your CE save DC and has hit points equal to 5 x the combined CR of the creatures used. You can move it 5 ft as a bonus action and can have only one wall at a time.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Human Weapon.</strong> As a bonus action, you form a creature into a simple or martial weapon or ammunition. The weapon gains a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls if the creature's CR is 5 or higher and increases by +1 per 5 CR to a maximum of +4.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>People Spikes.</strong> As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus, covering a 5 ft area per human on the ground within 30 ft of you with human spikes. A creature that walks through this area takes 2d8 piercing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Transfiguration Adept" supports="Transfiguration Adept" number="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Transfiguration Adept" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TRANSFIGURATION_ADEPT2">
		<prerequisite>Must have Transfiguration</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_TRANSFIGURATION_ADEPT1</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Transfiguration</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered your observation of the soul and learned grotesque molds to shape them into. You gain the two of the following ways to use transfigured humans (this feat can be repeated):</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Remote Transfiguration.</strong> When using Transfiguration, you can instead imprint a small, latent amount  of cursed energy upon their souls, allowing you to transfigure them from large distances (only one touch per creature).</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Wall of Flesh.</strong> As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus to form a flat panel of human flesh up to 5 ft long and wide per human used in an unoccupied space within 5 ft. The wall's AC equals your CE save DC and has hit points equal to 5 x the combined CR of the creatures used. You can move it 5 ft as a bonus action and can have only one wall at a time.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Human Weapon.</strong> As a bonus action, you form a creature into a simple or martial weapon or ammunition. The weapon gains a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls if the creature's CR is 5 or higher and increases by +1 per 5 CR to a maximum of +4.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>People Spikes.</strong> As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus, covering a 5 ft area per human on the ground within 30 ft of you with human spikes. A creature that walks through this area takes 2d8 piercing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Transfiguration Adept" supports="Transfiguration Adept" number="2" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Remote Transfiguration" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_REMOTE_TRANSFIGURATION">
		<supports>Transfiguration Adept</supports>
		<description>
			<p>When using Transfiguration, you can instead imprint a small, latent amount  of cursed energy upon their souls, allowing you to transfigure them from large distances (only one touch per creature).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When using Transfiguration, you can instead imprint latent CE, allowing you to transfigure them from large distances (only one touch per creature).</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Wall of Flesh" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_WALL_OF_FLESH">
		<supports>Transfiguration Adept</supports>
		<description>
			<p>As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus to form a flat panel of human flesh up to 5 ft long and wide per human used in an unoccupied space within 5 ft. The wall's AC equals your CE save DC and has hit points equal to 5 x the combined CR of the creatures used. You can move it 5 ft as a bonus action and can have only one wall at a time.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Spend up to {{proficiency}} humans to make a 5 ft long and wide wall per human used in an unoccupied space within 5 ft. The wall has {{ce:dc:total}} AC and hit points equal to 5 x the combined CR of the creatures used. You can move it 5 ft as a bonus action and can have only one wall at a time.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Human Weapon" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_HUMAN_WEAPON">
		<supports>Transfiguration Adept</supports>
		<description>
			<p>As a bonus action, you form a creature into a simple or martial weapon or ammunition. The weapon gains a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls if the creature's CR is 5 or higher and increases by +1 per 5 CR to a maximum of +4.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action">
			<description>Form a creature into a simple or martial weapon or ammunition. The weapon gains a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls if the creature's CR is 5 or higher and increases by +1 per 5 CR to a maximum of +4.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="People Spikes" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FEATURE_PEOPLE_SPIKES">
		<supports>Transfiguration Adept</supports>
		<description>
			<p>As an action, you spend humans up to your proficiency bonus, covering a 5 ft area per human on the ground within 30 ft of you with human spikes. A creature that walks through this area takes 2d8 piercing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Spend up to {{proficiency}} humans covering a 5 ft area per human on the ground within 30 ft of you with human spikes. A creature that walks through this area takes 2d8 piercing damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Awakening" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_AWAKENING">
		<prerequisite>Must have Alteration</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Alteration</em></p>
			<p>When you use Ally-Alteration on a Non-Sorcerer, you can instead spend 10 cursed energy to awaken the sorcerer, making a DC 25 Cursed Energy check to awaken the target. On a success, their potential grows over the course of 1d4 + 4 days, gaining a level in a Jujutsu Sorcerer class of the DM's choice. Roll a d100 to see if the target has an Innate Technique despite being a Non-Sorcerer. On a 99-100, the target has an innate technique.</p>
			<p class="indent">If you roll below a 15 on the Cursed Energy check, the target takes your Transfiguration damage, potentially making the target into a transfigured human.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you use Ally-Alteration on a Non-Sorcerer, you can instead spend 10 CE to make a DC 25 CE check. If you roll below a 15, the target takes your Transfiguration damage, potentially making the target into a transfigured human. On a success, their potential grows over the course of 1d4 + 4 days, gaining a level in a Jujutsu Sorcerer class of the DM's choice. Roll a d100 and on a 99-100, the target has an innate technique. </description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Soul Alteration" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SOUL_ALTERATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Body Clone</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Body Clone</em></p>
			<p>Your manipulation over your soul has increased dramatically, making you almost impossible to kill by those who cannot target your soul. When you use Self-Alteration, you can instead spend cursed energy up to your Cursed Energy modifier to regain 5 hit points per cursed energy spent. You can regrow a limb for every 2 cursed energy spent in this way. At 11th level, this instead becomes 10 hit points per CE, can be used as a reaction to damage, and costs 1 CE to regrow limbs.</p>
			<p class="indent">When you are reduced to 0 hit points while you have at least 1 CE, by a method that does not directly harm your soul, you are instead incapacitated until you regain hit points and do not make death saves. While incapacitated in this way, the only action you can take is to use Soul Alteration as an action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you use Self-Alteration, you can instead spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE to regain 5 hit points per CE spent. You can regrow a limb for every 2 CE spent in this way. When you are reduced to 0 hit points while you have at least 1 CE by a method that does not directly harm your soul, you are instead incapacitated until you regain hit points and do not make death saves. While incapacitated in this way, you can only use Soul Alteration as an action.</description>
			<description level="11">When you use Self-Alteration or as a reaction to damage, you can instead spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE to regain 10 hit points per CE spent. You can regrow a limb for every 1 CE spent in this way. When you are reduced to 0 hit points while you have at least 1 CE by a method that does not directly harm your soul, you are instead incapacitated until you regain hit points and do not make death saves. While incapacitated in this way, you can only use Soul Alteration as an action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Instant Spirit Body of Distorted Killing" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_DISTORTED_KILLING">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Self Embodiment of Perfection</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Self Embodiment of Perfection</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 8 cursed energy, you mold your body and soul into a form most befitting you. A form suited for killing. For 1 hour, your AC cannot be lower than 25 and you gain damage reduction equal to your CE modifier as your body has become impossibly hard and dense. Additionally, you gain elbow blades that count as simple melee weapons that you are proficient with. They deal 1d12 + your Cursed Energy modifier in piercing damage on a hit. When you make an attack with your Elbow Blades, you can spend 1 cursed energy to gain advantage on and increase the range of the attack to 15 feet as the Elbow Blade extends and shoots out at the target.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 8 CE, for 1 hour your AC cannot be lower than 25 and you gain {{ce:modifier}} damage reduction. Additionally, you gain elbow blades that count as simple melee weapons that you are proficient with which deal 1d12 + {{ce:modifier}} piercing damage on a hit. When you make an attack with your Elbow Blades, you can spend 1 CE to gain advantage and increase the range of the attack to 15 feet.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Illusive Mirage -->
	<element name="Funny Faces" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FUNNY_FACES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cursed Illusion</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ILLUSIVE_MIRAGE_CURSED_ILLUSION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Cursed Illusion</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to add a bit of humor to your technique. When a cursed creature sees a distorted face, you can spend 2 CE to force the Intelligence saving throw to be made at disadvantage by making the face look extra goofy. Additionally, you can spend 1 CE to change the distortion, causing them to have to make an additional Intelligence save on their next turn if they see a distorted face.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When a cursed creature sees a distorted face, you can spend 2 CE to force the Intelligence saving throw to be made at disadvantage. Additionally, you can spend 1 CE to have them make an additional Intelligence save on their next turn if they see a distorted face.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Cursed Tracking" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CURSED_TRACKING">
		<prerequisite>Must have Self Distortion</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ILLUSIVE_MIRAGE_SELF_DISTORTION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Self Distortion</em></p>
			<p>You have begun to work on your tracking skills over your illusions so you can track your targets at all times.</p>
			<p class="indent">When someone is cursed by your technique you can spend an additional 3 cursed energy to forgo the effects of the illusions but enhance the tracking. Somewhere on the target's body, a mark appears out of sight without their knowledge. They can make an Investigation check against your Cursed Energy DC to become aware of the curse or if someone else points it out. This mark will last for 24 hours and while it's active you will always have a precise location of the target within a range of 300 ft + your proficiency bonus x 100 ft. At the beginning of each day you can spend 5 Cursed Energy to keep it active for another 24 hours.</p>
			<p class="indent">If a target leaves your range, you cannot track them until they reenter your range. You cannot extend your tracking period if they are not within range.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 additional CE, you can forgo the effects of your illusions to place a mark on a cursed creature's body out of sight without their knowledge. They can make an Investigation check against your Cursed Energy DC to become aware of the curse or if someone else points it out. This mark lasts for 24 hours and while it's active you will always have a precise location of the target within a range of {{cursed:tracking:range}}. At the beginning of each day you can spend 5 CE to keep it active for another 24 hours. If a target leaves your range, you cannot track them until they reenter your range. You cannot extend your tracking period if they are not within range.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="cursed:tracking:range" value="300" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Absolute Perspective" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_ABSOLUTE_PERSPECTIVE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Illusive Terrain</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ILLUSIVE_MIRAGE_ILLUSIVE_TERRAIN</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Illusive Terrain</em></p>
			<p>For 10 cursed energy, you can force a creature in range to make a Cursed Energy saving throw at disadvantage. On a failure, you completely fool all of their senses for 1 minute. You can freely create illusions around the target as if they are under your Cursed Illusion or Illusive Terrain. They automatically fail checks to determine the illusions are fake as their mind rationalizes any inconsistencies. Additionally, the target believes so strongly that your illusions are real that they can actually take damage. Once per turn if you create a harmful illusion, the target can take psychic damage equal to your proficiency bonus in d6s.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, you can force a creature in range to make a CE saving throw at disadvantage. On a failure, for 1 minute you can freely create illusions around the target as if they are under your Cursed Illusion or Illusive Terrain. They automatically fail checks to determine the illusions are fake. Once per turn if you create a harmful illusion, the target takes {{proficiency}}d6 psychic damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Inverse -->
	<element name="Extreme Inverse" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EXTREME_INVERSE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Extreme Opposites</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_INVERSE_EXTREME_OPPOSITES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Extreme Opposites</em></p>
			<p>You have fully mastered your Inverse technique, allowing you to withstand devastating attacks while weak strikes take a heavy toll. When you take damage, the effect depends on whether it exceeds or falls below your threshold.</p>
			<p class="indent">If the damage exceeds your threshold, you reduce it by an amount equal to your level. However, if the damage is below your threshold, you increase the damage taken by an amount equal to your level. This makes you near-invulnerable to powerful blows, but even the lightest strike can prove perilous.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you take damage, if it exceeds your threshold reduce it by an additional {{level}} and if it is below increase it by an additional {{level}}. </description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Inverted Field" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_INVERTED_FIELD">
		<prerequisite>Must have Quick Inversion</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_INVERSE_QUICK_INVERSION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Quick Inversion</em></p>
			<p>While training on your technique, you have found out you have a lot more to offer than just being an indestructible powerhouse. You have learned how to alter a whole area to be affected by your technique. As a bonus action for 6 cursed energy, you cause all objects and creatures within 30 ft of you to be affected by your Inverse technique for 1 minute. A creature or object is no longer affected by Inverse if they leave the range of the field. You can deactivate this as a bonus action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 6 CE, all objects and creatures within 30 ft of you are affected by your Inverse technique for 1 minute. A creature or object is no longer affected by Inverse if they leave the range of the field. You can deactivate this as a bonus action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Antithesis" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_ANTITHESIS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Synesthesia</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_INVERSE_SYNAESTHESIA</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Synesthesia</em></p>
			<p>You've learned to channel your inverted energy outward, inverting the flow of harm itself while your Inverse is active:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>When you take damage within your threshold, you can spend 4 CE as a reaction to reflect half of that damage back to the attacker (damage becomes force or necrotic, your choice) if they are within 30 ft.</li>
				<li>When you take damage below your threshold, you can instead spend 1 CE as a free action to transfer the pain. Choose a creature within 30 ft to take force or necrotic damage (your choice) equal to twice your CE modifier.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>While Inverse is active, when you take damage above your threshold, you can spend 4 CE as a reaction to reflect half of that damage back to the attacker as necrotic or force damage if they are within 30 ft. You may also spend 1 CE as a free action when you take damage below your threshold to choose a creature within 30 ft to take {{inverse:antithesis:damage}} necrotic or force damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="inverse:antithesis:damage" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="inverse:antithesis:damage" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Limitless -->
	<element name="Spatial Skirmishing" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SPATIAL_SKIRMISHING">
		<prerequisite>Must have Lapse Blue</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Lapse Blue</em></p>
			<p>Through intense training and familiarizing yourself with your technique, you have gained the ability to apply Lapse Blue to your fists. Once per turn, when you make an unarmed strike, by spending cursed energy you can make them suffer the effects of Lapse Blue on a hit. For this attack you can use your cursed energy modifier for attack rolls. When you use Lapse Blue in this way, the target takes additional damage equal to Lapse Blue on a hit and you gain advantage on that attack roll as your technique attracts the target.</p>
			<p class="indent">If you have access to Reversal Red, you can also imbue Red to your fists. When you use Red in this way, the target takes additional damage equal to Reversal Red on a hit and must make a Strength saving throw or be launched the same distance as a normal Red.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>Once per turn when you make an unarmed strike, you can apply Lapse Blue spending up to its limit in CE. You can use your CE modifier for this attack roll and have advantage on the attack. On a hit, the target takes the Lapse Blue damage. You can do the same with Reversal Red, being able to use your CE modifier for this attack roll. On a hit, the target takes the Reversal Red damage and must make a Strength saving throw or be launched the same distance as a normal Red.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Hollow Purple" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_HOLLOW_PURPLE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Lapse Blue and Reversal Red</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE,ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_REVERSAL_RED</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Lapse Blue and Reversal Red</em></p>
			<p>You have learned how to mix positive and negative space, creating imaginary mass. After using your action to prepare the technique, you can release it as an action for 10 Cursed Energy. Every creature in a 5 feet wide 100-foot line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they take 20d12 force damage, are moved to the end of the line, gain 1 level of exhaustion and you can target a limb from the Limb Damage Table. On a successful save, they take half as much damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, prepare a Hollow Purple. As an later action, every creature in a 5 feet wide 100-foot line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they take 20d12 force damage, are moved to the end of the line, gain 1 level of exhaustion and you can target a limb from the Limb Damage Table. On a successful save, they take half as much damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Delayed Purple" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DELAYED_PURPLE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Hollow Purple</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_HOLLOW_PURPLE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Hollow Purple</em></p>
			<p>You have found a new more powerful way to fire Purple. As a reaction or action when a Blue is active, you can shoot a Red into it if it is within range. This forcefully creates a Hollow Purple that affects everything in a 100 foot radius around the source. This Hollow Purple deals maximum damage on a failed save or half as much on a success. You must also make a saving throw if you are within range. This technique cannot be used at Maximum Output.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action/Reaction">
			<description>When a Blue is active, you can shoot a Red into it if it is within range. This creates a Hollow Purple that deals maximum damage on a failed save or half as much on a success to everything in a 100 ft radius around the Blue. This technique cannot be used at Maximum Output.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Love Rendezvous -->
	<element name="Comet Reactions" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_COMET_REACTIONS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Effective Marking</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LOVE_RENDEZVOUS_EFFECTIVE_MARKING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Effective Marking</em></p>
			<p>Your reaction speed has further increased. At the cost of one CE, you gain the ability to use the reactions from effective markings for other purposes.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 1 CE, you can use the reactions from Effective Marking for other purposes.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Repelling Forces" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_REPELLING_FORCES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Gravity</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LOVE_RENDEZVOUS_GRAVITY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Gravity</em></p>
			<p>You have gained further variety with your Marks and the forces within it. As a bonus action for up to 3 CE you can force marked creatures to be repelled from the creature with the highest amount of CE. How far depends on how much CE you use, with them moving 10 feet for every CE. They take 2d8 bludgeoning damage if the repelled movement forces them into a structure, object, or creature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For up to 3 CE, force marked creatures to be repelled from the creature with the highest amount of CE moving 10 feet for every CE spent. They take 2d8 bludgeoning damage if the repelled movement forces them into a structure, object, or creature.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Star Crossed" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_STAR_CROSSED">
		<prerequisite>Must have Shining Stars</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LOVE_RENDEZVOUS_SHINING_STARS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Shining Stars</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 10 CE, you push yourself and mark a creature you touch with all your power. Marking a creature this way, attracts one body into itself causing massive damage. When you activate this, the creature must make a Constitution saving throw, taking 25d4 force damage and a level of exhaustion on a failed save or half as much on a success.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, touch a creature and force them to make a Constitution saving throw, taking 25d4 force damage and a level of exhaustion on a failed save or half as much on a success.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Miracle -->
	<element name="Beginner's Luck" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BEGINNERS_LUCK">
		<prerequisite>Must have Little Miracles</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Little Miracles</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to more efficiently store up luck. You can now store an additional number of Miracles equal to your CE modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<stat name="miracle:max" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Blessing of Fortune" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLESSING_OF_FORTUNE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Miraculous Outcome</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Miraculous Outcome</em></p>
			<p>When you or a creature you can see fails a death saving throw, you can spend 1 Miracle and 1 CE as a reaction. The roll is now considered a natural 20. You cannot experience a breakthrough or gain a Miracle in this way.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="Miracle+CE">
			<description>For 1 Miracle and 1 CE as a reaction to you or a creature failing a death saving throw, the roll is now considered a natural 20. You cannot experience a breakthrough or gain a Miracle in this way.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Innate Luck" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_INNATE_LUCK">
		<prerequisite>Must have Fated for Fortune</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Fated for Fortune</em></p>
			<p>Some have asked you: "Are you lucky because you have miracles by your side, or do you have miracles by your side because you're lucky?" The answer was obvious, you are naturally lucky and your technique merely reflects that. You roll all dice generated by your cursed technique twice, picking the result of the higher one. Additionally, you can make a miracle die roll its maximum amount once per long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You roll all dice generated by your cursed technique twice, picking the result of the higher one. Additionally, you can make a miracle die roll its maximum amount once per long rest.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Missile Fist -->
	<element name="Exploding Fighting Spirit" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EXPLODING_FIGHTING_SPIRIT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Missile Impact</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MISSILE_FIST_MISSILE_IMPACT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Missile Impact</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to channel your passion for battle and fighting spirit into your cursed technique. When you hit a creature with Missile Fist, all creatures within 5 ft (other than you) take thunder damage equal to your CE modifier from the shockwaves. You can use this effect a number of times each turn equal to your proficiency bonus. When you hit a target with a Missile Fist, you gain a +1 bonus to attack rolls against that target. This bonus can stack and lasts until the end of your turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you hit a creature with Missile Fist, all creatures within 5 ft other than you take {{ce:modifier}} thunder damage. You can use this effect {{proficiency}} times each turn. When you hit a target with a Missile Fist, you gain a +1 bonus to attack rolls against that target. This bonus can stack and lasts until the end of your turn.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Armored Missile Fist" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ARMORED_MISSILE_FIST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Devastating Barrage</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MISSILE_FIST_DEVASTATING_BARRAGE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Devastating Barrage</em></p>
			<p>As a bonus action for 2 CE, you cover your hands in Missile Fists, gaining the following benefits for 1 minute.</p>
			<ul>
				<li>You gain a +2 bonus to AC while holding no weapons or shields.</li>
				<li>You can use your CE modifier for attack and damage rolls using your unarmed strikes.</li>
				<li>Your unarmed strikes deal your Missile Fist damage.</li>
				<li>The range of your unarmed strikes becomes 10 ft.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, for 1 minute you gain a +2 bonus to AC while holding no weapons or shields, can use your CE modifier for attack and damage rolls using your unarmed strikes, your unarmed strikes deal your Missile Fist damage, and the range of your unarmed strikes becomes 10 ft.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Titan's Grasp" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TITANS_GRASP">
		<prerequisite>Must have Unrelenting Fury</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MISSILE_FIST_UNRELENTING_FURY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Unrelenting Fury</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction for 3 CE, when you or a creature within 30 ft would take damage, you interpose a Missile Fist, reducing the damage by your Missile Fist damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, when you or a creature within 30 ft would take damage you reduce it by your Missile Fist damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Moon Dregs -->
	<element name="Immortal Jellyfish" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_IMMORTAL_JELLYFISH">
		<prerequisite>Must have Lunar Jellyfish</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOON_DREGS_LUNAR_JELLYFISH</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Lunar Jellyfish</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to reinforce your shikigami with cursed energy. As part of the bonus action to command Moon Dregs, you can spend cursed energy up to your Cursed Energy modifier to give Moon Dregs 5 temporary hit points per Cursed Energy spent. This increases to 10 temporary hit points per cursed energy at 11th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>As part of the bonus action to command Moon Dregs, you can spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE to give Moon Dregs {{moon:dregs:immortal:temp:hp}} temporary hit points per Cursed Energy spent.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="moon:dregs:immortal:temp:hp" value="5" bonus="immortal jellyfish" />
			<stat name="moon:dregs:immortal:temp:hp" value="10" bonus="immortal jellyfish" level="11" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Adorable Poison Jar" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ADORABLE_POISON_JAR">
		<prerequisite>Must have Poisonous Cursed Energy</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOON_DREGS_POISONOUS_CURSED_ENERGY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Poisonous Cursed Energy</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to refine your poisons within Moon Dregs to create powerful mixtures. You gain the following benefits:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Moon Dregs deals an additional 1d6 poison damage on a hit. This increases to 2d6 at 6th level and 3d8 at 11th level.</li>
				<li>A creature grappled by Moon Dregs takes 2d4 poison damage at the beginning of their turn. This increases to 2d8 poison damage at 11th level.</li>
				<li>Poison can also be used as an enhancer. You gain 4 ability points you can use to increase Moon Dregs ability scores (max of 20).</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Moon Dregs deals an additional 1d6 poison damage on a hit. A creature grappled by Moon Dregs takes 2d4 poison damage at the beginning of their turn. You gain 4 ability points you can use to increase Moon Dregs ability scores (max of 20).</description>
			<description level="6">Moon Dregs deals an additional 2d6 poison damage on a hit. A creature grappled by Moon Dregs takes 2d4 poison damage at the beginning of their turn. You gain 4 ability points you can use to increase Moon Dregs ability scores (max of 20).</description>
			<description level="11">Moon Dregs deals an additional 3d8 poison damage on a hit. A creature grappled by Moon Dregs takes 2d8 poison damage at the beginning of their turn. You gain 4 ability points you can use to increase Moon Dregs ability scores (max of 20).</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Crippling Neurotoxin" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_NEUROTOXIN">
		<prerequisite>Must have Cleansing of Purity</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MOON_DREGS_CLEANSING_PURITY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p> You have finally learned to amplify your poisonous cursed energy into a crippling neurotoxin that locks down nerves. When you use Poisonous Cursed Energy, you can spend 8 additional cursed energy to enhance the poison. If a creature fails their save against Noxious Poison they are stunned until the end of their next turn and poisoned for 8 hours. On a successful save, the target is poisoned for 1 minute. A creature poisoned in this way is treated as being under 3 temporary levels of exhaustion. If a creature fails the save by 5 or more, they are paralyzed until the end of their next turn and poisoned for 24 hours.</p>
			<p class="indent"> This poison ignores cursed techniques that grant resistance, immunity, or other reductions to poison damage and the poisoned condition. This poison cannot be removed by cursed techniques or reverse cursed technique.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you use Poisonous Cursed Energy, you can spend 8 additional CE to stun the creature until the end of their next turn and give them the poisoned condition for 8 hours if they fail the save. On a successful save, the target is poisoned for 1 minute. A creature poisoned in this way is treated as being under 3 temporary levels of exhaustion. If a creature fails the save by 5 or more, they are paralyzed until the end of their next turn and poisoned for 24 hours.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Mythical Beast Amber -->
	<element name="Defensive Surge" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DEFENSIVE_SURGE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Electric Energy</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MYTHICAL_BEAST_AMBER_ELECTRIC_ENERGY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Electric Energy</em></p>
			<p>Your Cursed Energy has gained a defensive property. As a reaction to being hit by a melee attack, you can spend 2 CE to force the attacker to make a Constitution Saving Throw. On a failure, the creature is paralyzed until the beginning of their next turn.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>As a reaction to being hit by a melee attack, you can spend 2 CE to force the attacker to make a Constitution Saving Throw. On a failure, the creature is paralyzed until the beginning of their next turn.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Imbued Weapon" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_IMBUED_WEAPON">
		<prerequisite>Must have Lightning Discharge</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MYTHICAL_BEAST_AMBER_LIGHTNING_DISCHARGE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Lightning Discharge</em></p>
			<p>You have learned how to further manipulate your lightning. On a hit with a melee attack using a weapon it also gains a charge, and as a bonus action you can release a bolt of lightning between the weapon and yourself. Those caught in that bolt of lightning must make a Dexterity save, taking your Lightning Discharge damage on a failure or half as much on a success.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>On a hit with a melee attack using a weapon it also gains a charge, and as a bonus action you can release a bolt of lightning between the weapon and yourself. Those caught in that bolt of lightning must make a Dexterity save, taking your Lightning Discharge damage on a failure or half as much on a success.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Grounded Charge" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_GROUNDED_CHARGE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Mythical Beast Amber Release</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MYTHICAL_BEAST_AMBER_RELEASE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Mythical Beast Amber Release</em></p>
			<p>Through repeated usage of your cursed technique's release your body has grown used to the manifestation of phenomena. The side effects of using Mythical Beast Amber: Release are reduced by 1 stage. This causes stage 0 to have no side effects.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>The side effects of using Mythical Beast Amber Release are reduced by 1 stage. This causes stage 0 to have no side effects.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- New Shadow Style -->
	<element name="True New Shadow Style" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TRUE_NEW_SHADOW_STYLE">
		<prerequisite>Must have New Shadow Style: Simple Domain</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_NEW_SHADOW_STYLE_SIMPLE_DOMAIN</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have New Shadow Style: Simple Domain</em></p>
			<p>Your Simple Domain now has additional hit points equal to twice your Cursed Energy modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your Simple Domain has {{true:shadow:style:hp}} additional hit points.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="true:shadow:style:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="true:shadow:style:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Instantaneous Attack" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_INSTANTANEOUS_ATTACK">
		<prerequisite>Must have Batto Sword Draw</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_NEW_SHADOW_STYLE_BATTO_SWORD_DRAW</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Batto Sword Draw</em></p>
			<p>You have learned the fastest way to draw defensively. Once per round after activating Simple Domain, you can make a melee attack against someone who enters it.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Once per round after activating Simple Domain, you can make a melee attack against someone who enters it.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="First Strike" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FIRST_STRIKE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Evening Moon Sword Drawing</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_NEW_SHADOW_STYLE_EVENING_MOON_SWORD_DRAWING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Evening Moon Sword Drawing</em></p>
			<p>You have honed your reaction speed to the finest edge. When you roll initiative you can activate Simple Domain or make an attack as a free action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you roll initiative you can activate Simple Domain or make an attack as a free action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maculation" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MACULATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Moonlight Veil</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_NEW_SHADOW_STYLE_MOONLIGHT_VEIL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Moonlight Veil</em></p>
			<p>As an action for up to 6 cursed energy, you create up to 6 smaller Simple Domains on the ground within 30 ft of yourself that each cover a 5 ft space for 1 minute. Each Maculation functions as a Simple Domain with hit points equal to 5 x your proficiency bonus. While standing in a space with Maculation, you can use your reaction to either gain a +3 bonus to AC or reduce incoming damage by your weapon's damage until the beginning of your next turn. A Maculation disappears if you end your turn more than 30 ft away from one.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For up to 6 CE, create up to 6 smaller Simple Domains within 30 ft that each cover a 5 ft space for 1 minute. Each has {{new:shadow:style:maculation:hp}} hit points. While standing in one, you can use your reaction to gain +3 AC or reduce incoming damage by your weapon's damage until the beginning of your next turn.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="new:shadow:style:maculation:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="new:shadow:style:maculation:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="new:shadow:style:maculation:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="new:shadow:style:maculation:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="new:shadow:style:maculation:hp" value="proficiency" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Pachinko Fever -->
	<element name="Contagious Luck" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CONTAGIOUS_LUCK">
		<prerequisite>Must have Great Luck</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PACHINKO_FEVER_GREAT_LUCK</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Great Luck</em></p>
			<p>Your luck seems to spread to those around you. You can use Great Luck on another creature of your choice instead of yourself.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can use Great Luck on another creature of your choice instead of yourself.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Pachinko Manifest" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PACHINKO_MANIFEST">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Idle Death Gamble</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PACHINKO_FEVER_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_IDLE_DEATH_GAMBLE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Idle Death Gamble</em></p>
			<p>Through thorough understanding of your domain, you can now manifest Pachinko Attacks outside your domain and have a 30 foot range when used this way. Whenever you use a Pachinko Attack, you add your Cursed Energy modifier to the damage rolls. Additionally, you reduce the Cursed Energy cost of your Pachinko Attacks by 1 CE. This reduces the CE cost of Green Balls to 0 CE, but cannot reduce the CE cost of other Pachinko Attacks to 0 CE (minimum of 1). These attacks do not build Expectation.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Pachinko Attacks can be used outside your domain with a range of 30 ft. You add {{ce:modifier}} to their damage rolls and reduce their CE cost by 1 (Green Balls to 0, others minimum 1). These attacks do not build Expectation.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Love Train" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_LOVE_TRAIN">
		<prerequisite>Must have The Fever</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PACHINKO_FEVER_THE_FEVER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have The Fever</em></p>
			<p>You have fully understood the essence of your technique. As an action for 10 Cursed Energy, you can summon the Love Train. This is a 200 foot long, 20 feet wide Line attack in which a creature within range must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure they are launched 200 feet and take 15d6 bludgeoning damage. The train is summoned on a space of your choice within 30ft, and the opponent is launched in the opposite direction.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, summon a train on a space of your choice within 30 ft, forcing creatures within a 200 ft long, 20 ft wide line to make a Dexterity save or be launched 200 ft and take 15d6 bludgeoning damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Pain Killer -->
	<element name="Dull Pain" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DULL_PAIN">
		<prerequisite>Must have Pain Killer</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PAIN_KILLER_PAIN_KILLER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Pain Killer</em></p>
			<p>A creature under the effects of Pain Killer now gains additional temporary hit points equal to 5 times your proficiency bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<stat name="pain:killer:temp:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="pain:killer:temp:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="pain:killer:temp:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="pain:killer:temp:hp" value="proficiency" />
			<stat name="pain:killer:temp:hp" value="proficiency" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Long Lasting Medicine" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_LONG_LASTING_MEDICINE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Practiced Hands</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PAIN_KILLER_PRACTICED_HANDS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Practiced Hands</em></p>
			<p>A creature now gains the benefits of Pain Killer for 24 hours and is automatically stabilized if they are reduced to 0 hit points while under the effect.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>A creature with Pain Killer is automatically stabilized if reduced to 0 hit points.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Panacea" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_PANACEA">
		<prerequisite>Must have Analgesic</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PAIN_KILLER_ANALGESIC</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Analgesic</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction to a creature within 10 feet (including yourself) falling to 0 hit points you can spend 4 CE and cause them to instead remain at 10 hit points and gain the benefits of Pain Killer.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>When a creature within 10 ft falls to 0 hit points, you can spend 4 CE to have them remain at 10 hit points and gain the benefits of Pain Killer.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Paralyzing Gaze -->
	<element name="Immobilized Limbs" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_IMMOBILIZED_LIMBS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Immobilizing Eyes</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PARALYZING_GAZE_IMMOBILIZING_EYES</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Immobilizing Eyes</em></p>
			<p>When you use Immobilizing Eyes, you can spend 1 additional CE as part of activating the technique concentrate your eyes on a specific part of the creature, also causing one of the following restrictions while you maintain your technique:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Legs.</strong> The target's speed is halved. If the target tries to move more than their movement speed, they must make a Dexterity saving throw or fall prone.</li>
				<li><strong>Arms.</strong> The target gains an additional -3 penalty to attack rolls and cannot take object interactions.</li>
				<li><strong>Torso.</strong> You reduce the target's AC by 3.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you use Immobilizing Eyes, you can spend 1 additional CE to halve the target's speed and force them to make a Dexterity saving throw or fall prone if they move more than their movement speed, give them -3 to attack rolls and prevent them from taking object interactions, or reduce their AC by 3.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Destructive Gaze" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DESTRUCTIVE_GAZE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Peripheral Vision</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PARALYZING_GAZE_PERIPHERAL_VISION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Peripheral Vision</em></p>
			<p>As part of your bonus action while maintaining your technique on a creature, the target takes 2d8 psychic damage. This increases to 2d10 at 6th level, 4d8 at 11th level, and 6d8 at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>As part of your bonus action while maintaining your technique on a creature, the target takes 2d8 psychic damage.</description>
			<description level="6">As part of your bonus action while maintaining your technique on a creature, the target takes 2d10 psychic damage.</description>
			<description level="11">As part of your bonus action while maintaining your technique on a creature, the target takes 4d8 psychic damage.</description>
			<description level="18">As part of your bonus action while maintaining your technique on a creature, the target takes 6d8 psychic damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Eye Drops" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EYE_DROPS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Reactive Eye Movement</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PARALYZING_GAZE_REACTIVE_EYE_MOVEMENT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Reactive Eye Movement</em></p>
			<p>Through constant exposure, your eyes have become surprisingly tough. Whenever your eyes take damage, the damage is halved. When your eyes' hit points would be reduced to 0 hit points, you can make a DC 20 Constitution saving throw for your eyes to stay at 1 hit point. If you have Reverse Cursed Technique, you automatically succeed. You can make this saving throw a number of times equal to your proficiency bonus each long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Damage to your eyes is halved. When your eyes' hit points would be reduced to 0 hit points, you can make a DC 20 Constitution saving throw for your eyes to stay at 1 hit point. If you have Reverse Cursed Technique, you automatically succeed. You can make this saving throw {{proficiency}} times per long rest.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Prayer Song -->
	<element name="Fortissimo" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FORTISSIMO">
		<prerequisite>Must have Marcado</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PRAYER_SONG_MARCADO</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Marcado</em></p>
			<p>Once per turn, when you hit a creature with an attack while Prayer is active, you can spend 3 CE to deal maximum damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>Once per turn when you hit while Prayer is active, you can spend 3 CE to deal maximum damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Cadence" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CADENCE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Caesura</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PRAYER_SONG_CAESURA</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Caesura</em></p>
			<p>You put a full stop to the rhythm of your enemy. As a reaction, you can spend 3 CE to make an attack miss, or spend 5 CE to make a creature fail a saving throw.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE make an attack miss or for 5 CE make a creature fail a saving throw.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Double Time" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_DOUBLE_TIME">
		<prerequisite>Must have Crescendo</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PRAYER_SONG_CRESCENDO</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Crescendo</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 3 CE, you double the tempo of your song and the battle. You treat every turn as if two turns passed.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, treat every turn as if two turns passed.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Projection Sorcery -->
	<element name="White Space" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WHITE_SPACE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Acceleration</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PROJECTION_SORCERY_ACCELERATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Acceleration</em></p>
			<p>As a reaction to an attack or damaging effect, you can spend 2 cursed energy to create a number of blank animation frames to absorb any damage. Roll a number of d10s equal to 2 + your CE modifier. Any damage you take before the start of your next turn instead damages these blank frames, but you take any remaining damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, roll {{projection:sorcery:white:space:dr}}d10s that reduce any damage you take before the start of your next turn. You take any remaining damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="projection:sorcery:white:space:dr" value="2" />
			<stat name="projection:sorcery:white:space:dr" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Air Shatter" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_AIR_SHATTER">
		<prerequisite>Must have 24 Frame Rule</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PROJECTION_SORCERY_24_FRAME_RULE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have 24 Frame Rule</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 4 cursed energy, you create a 5 ft wide, 30 foot long line of frames in the air that you explosively break. All creatures in that line must make a Dexterity saving throw or take a number d10s in force damage equal to your CE modifier and are knocked prone. On a failed save, they take half as much damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 4 CE, creatures in a 5 ft by 30 ft line must make a Dexterity save or take {{ce:modifier}}d10 force damage and be knocked prone. On a failed save, they take half damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Sakuga" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SAKUGA">
		<prerequisite>Must have Fastest Sorcerer Alive</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PROJECTION_SORCERY_FASTEST_SORCERER_ALIVE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Fastest Sorcerer Alive</em></p>
			<p>When you activate your cursed energy you can force it past its limit for short periods of time. For an additional cursed energy per round, you also gain the following effects in addition to the other effects of your technique:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Your speed is doubled</li>
				<li>You gain advantage on Dexterity saves</li>
				<li>Your Dexterity score increases by +2, ignoring your maximum</li>
				<li>An additional action on each of your turns. That action can be used only to take the Attack action (one weapon attack only), Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object action.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For an additional CE per round while your technique is active, your speed is doubled, you have advantage on Dexterity saves, your Dexterity score increases by 2 ignoring your maximum, and you gain an additional action that can be used to Attack, Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Puppet Manipulation -->
	<element name="Puppet Armor" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PUPPET_ARMOR">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ultimate Mechamaru</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PUPPET_MANIPULATION_ULTIMATE_MECHAMARU</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ultimate Mechamaru</em></p>
			<p>As an action, you can wear your puppet, this gives you your puppets HP as temporary, as well as traits and physical stats and also increases your AC by 2.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Wear a puppet gaining its HP as temporary HP, its traits and physical stats, and +2 AC.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Communication Puppets" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_COMMUNICATION_PUPPETS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Lesser Puppet</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PUPPET_MANIPULATION_LESSER_PUPPET</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Lesser Puppet</em></p>
			<p>After one long rest, you create a small puppet that can fit on the palm of your hand. This puppet holds a copy of consciousness when you created it and has enough charge for five minutes. You can have a number equal to your proficiency bonus and anything learned by one is shared to all. These can be activated as a free action or set to activate after a specific trigger.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>After one long rest, you create a small puppet that can fit on the palm of your hand. You can create up to {{proficiency}} small puppets. This puppet holds a copy of consciousness when you created it and has enough charge for five minutes. These can be activated as a free action or set to activate after a specific trigger.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Ultimate Puppet" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_ULTIMATE_PUPPET">
		<prerequisite>Must have Absolute Puppet</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_PUPPET_MANIPULATION_ABSOLUTE_PUPPET</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Absolute Puppet</em></p>
			<p>You gain the ability to make a puppet of your Ultimate Puppet. This puppet can have double the traits, however it also costs double the resources, time, and Cursed Energy to create.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can create a puppet with double traits, but it costs double resources, time, and CE.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Ratio -->
	<element name="Focused Attacks" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FOCUSED_ATTACKS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Critical Focus</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_RATIO_CRITICAL_FOCUS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Critical Focus</em></p>
			<p>You gain a +1 bonus to your critical range.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You gain a +1 to your critical range.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Weapon Breaker" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WEAPON_BREAKER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Collapse</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_RATIO_COLLAPSE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Collapse</em></p>
			<p>You focus your Ratio on your opponent's weapon. When you are targeted by a weapon attack, you can spend 5 CE as a reaction to create and hit a vulnerable ratio point on their weapon, forcing them to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure the weapon breaks. If the weapon is a cursed tool, you must use a tool of equal or greater rank to break it, otherwise the attack fails. If used against an unarmed strike, it is treated as a limb damaging effect using the Limb Damage table. Roll critical damage with your weapon. If you deal the required damage, you break the limb. Either way, the target takes no damage and this feature cannot remove a limb.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When targeted by a weapon attack, for 5 CE force them to make a Dex save. On a failure, break the weapon. If the weapon is a cursed tool, you must use a tool of equal or greater rank to break it, otherwise the attack fails. If used against an unarmed strike, it is treated as a limb damaging effect using the Limb Damage table. Roll critical damage with your weapon. If you deal the required damage, you break the limb.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Deadly Ratio" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_DEADLY_RATIO">
		<prerequisite>Must have Improved Ratio</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_RATIO_IMPROVED_RATIO</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Improved Ratio</em></p>
			<p>For an additional 6 Cursed Energy, when you land a critical hit using ratio your target automatically loses a limb that is not the head or torso, using the limb damage table.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you land a critical hit using Ratio, you can spend 6 CE to cause the target to automatically lose a limb using the limb damage table (not head or torso).</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Rockstar -->
	<element name="Musical Climax" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MUSICAL_CLIMAX">
		<prerequisite>Must have Sound Amplification</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROCKSTAR_SOUND_AMPLIFICATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Sound Amplification</em></p>
			<p>You've learned that just playing isn't enough, you need to build up to the best part. As an action you can start playing your instrument to charge up your technique. You can charge your technique using your action this way for a number of times equal to your CE modifier while concentrating, after which you must release your technique. You can use your reaction to launch either a Sound Blast or Sound Wave at any time while playing this way and add 2 damage die per action you use to play before releasing and ignore resistances.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>Charge up your technique. You can charge your technique {{ce:modifier}} times after which you must release your technique. You can use your reaction to launch either a Sound Blast or Sound Wave that ignore resistances at any time while playing this way and add 2 damage die per charge.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Emotional Melodies" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EMOTIONAL_MELODIES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Resonating Music</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROCKSTAR_RESONATING_MUSIC</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Resonating Music</em></p>
			<p>As a bonus action for 5 cursed energy, you can introduce a vibe of your choice for 1 minute while concentrating. You can only have one Vibe active at a time. Deafened creatures automatically succeed.</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Happy Vibes.</strong> Your music gives happy and upbeat vibes. On a hit with your Sound Blast, the target makes a Charisma saving throw or be Charmed and only hear you and your music until the Vibe ends. They can repeat the save at the beginning of their turn.</li>
				<li><strong>Sad Vibes.</strong> Your music gives sad and depressed vibes, bringing the mood down. On a hit with your Sound Blast, the target makes a Charisma saving throw or fall prone and their speed becomes 0 until the Vibe ends. They can repeat the save at the beginning of their turn.</li>
				<li><strong>Angry Vibes.</strong> Your music gives off angry and rebellious vibes! On a hit with your Sound Blast, the target makes a Charisma saving throw or becomes berserk until the Vibe ends. A berserk creature uses their reaction to make a melee attack at the closest creature at the start of their turn and must use their action to attack. They can repeat the save at the beginning of their turn.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 CE, for 1 minute while concentrating, on a hit with your Sound Blast the target suffers an effect until you lose concentration if they fail a Charisma save which deafened creatures automatically suceed. They are either charmed and can only hear you, prone and their speed becomes 0, or must use thier reaction to make a melee attack at the closest creature at the start of their turn and can only use their action to attack. A creature can repeat the save at the beginning of their turn. You can only have one option active at a time.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Rock Squad" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ROCK_SQUAD">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Epic Solo</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROCKSTAR_MAXIMUM_EPIC_SOLO</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Epic Solo</em></p>
			<p>Looks like the band is getting back together! An epic guitar solo is always welcome, but people came for a show. When an allied creature ends their turn within 15 feet of you during your Epic Solo, their next attack or technique deals additional d4 in thunder damage equal to your proficiency bonus.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When an allied creature ends their turn within 15 feet of you during your Epic Solo, their next attack or technique deals {{proficiency}}d4 more thunder damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Rot -->
	<element name="Condensed Decay" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CONDENSED_DECAY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Scarlet Rot</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROT_SCARLET_ROT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Scarlet Rot</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to increase the potency of your blood's properties. When you use a Rot Technique, you can spend additional HP up to twice your CE modifier to increase the damage dice of acid dealt by your technique by one tier for every 2 HP spent (d8-d10-d12) to a max of d12.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use a Rot Technique, you can spend up to {{rot:condensed:decay:hp}} additional HP to increase the damage dice of acid dealt by your technique by one tier for every 2 HP spent to a max of d12.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="rot:condensed:decay:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="rot:condensed:decay:hp" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Blackened Blood" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLACKENED_BLOOD">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Wing King</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROT_MAXIMUM_WING_KING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Wing King</em></p>
			<p>Your blood has become bubbling and black. A creature that fails a Constitution saving throw against your technique by 5 or more gains a level of exhaustion. A creature cannot gain more than 3 levels of exhaustion from this feature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>A creature that fails a Constitution saving throw against your technique by 5 or more gains a level of exhaustion. A creature cannot gain more than 3 levels of exhaustion from this feature.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Wing King Improvement" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_WING_KING_IMPROVEMENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Wing King</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_ROT_MAXIMUM_WING_KING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Wing King</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered your Maximum technique, granting you the following benefits while using Wing King:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>You gain the Evasion feature</li>
				<li>You can now make four lines of blood attacks as a free action on your turn</li>
				<li>You can use a Rot Technique as a bonus action</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While using Maximum: Wing King, you can use Evasion and use a Rot Technique as a bonus action.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_ROGUE_EVASION" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Seance -->
	<element name="Gatherer of the Dead" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_GATHERER_OF_THE_DEAD">
		<prerequisite>Must have Seance</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEANCE_SEANCE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Seance</em></p>
			<p>While some may call you morbid, you are great at finding the corpses of deceased people. You gain proficiency in Investigation or expertise if already proficient, and will gain advantage on Intelligence (Investigation) and (History) checks related to dead humanoids and their techniques.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You have advantage on Investigation and History checks related to dead humanoids and their techniques.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Grants" id="ID_INTERNAL_GRANTS_PROFICIENCY_SKILL_OR_DOUBLE_INVESTIGATION" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Perfect Ritual" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PERFECT_RITUAL">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ritual of Resurrection</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEANCE_RITUAL_OF_RESURRECTION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ritual of Resurrection</em></p>
			<p>You won't allow anyone to interrupt your seance. You have advantage on saving throws to maintain concentration for your Seance technique and the time to complete your Ritual is decreased to 3 rounds. Additionally, you decrease the saving throw DC a target makes against the dead humanoid's Soul Information by your CE modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You have advantage on concentration saves for Seance, reduce Ritual of Resurrection time to 3 rounds, and decrease Soul Information's save DC by {{ce:modifier}}.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Cling to Life" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CLING_TO_LIFE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Black Seance</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SEANCE_MAXIMUM_BLACK_SEANCE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Black Seance</em></p>
			<p>When a target runs out of cursed energy and can no longer maintain the seance, they can choose to forcefully hold the spirit within their body. At the beginning of the target's turn, they instead spend 5 HP, reducing their maximum by the same amount. Your hit point maximum is restored by 15 after each long rest.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When a target runs out of CE in a Seance body, at the beginning of the target's turn they can instead spend 5 HP, reducing their maximum by the same amount. Their hit point maximum is restored by 15 after each long rest.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Shrine -->
	<element name="Spiderweb" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SPIDERWEB">
		<prerequisite>Must have Dismantle</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SHRINE_DISMANTLE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Dismantle</em></p>
			<p>Your Dismantle attack has grown into more versatility. For an extra 1 Cursed energy you can make Dismantle into a 30 ft cone which deals critical damage to structures, creating difficult terrain and forcing a Dexterity saving throw for all creatures within range, taking Dismantle's damage on a failed save.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For an extra 1 CE, Dismantle becomes a 30 ft cone that forces a Dexterity save for all creatures in range, taking Dismantle's damage on a failed save. This also creates difficult terrain and does critical damage to structures.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Disassembly" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DISASSEMBLY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Slicing and Severing</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SHRINE_SLICING_AND_SEVERING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Slicing and Severing</em></p>
			<p>You have learned to further segment your attacks to target more creatures. When you spend more than 1 CE for Dismantle, you can instead fire multiple slashes splitting damage die between the slashes before attacking and making a separate attack roll for each.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When spending more than 1 CE on Dismantle, you can split damage dice into multiple slashes before attacking and make separate attack rolls for each one.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: World Cleave" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_WORLD_CLEAVE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Malevolent Shrine</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SHRINE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_MALEVOLENT_SHRINE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Malevolent Shrine</em></p>
			<p>You have broadened the understanding of your technique, cutting the area your target is in instead of the target itself. When you spend the maximum amount of cursed energy on Cleave, you can instead create a 5 ft wide, 10 ft long line in a point within 60 ft that you can see. Any creature in range must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure they take maximum damage, on a success they take half as much damage. This damage ignores resistances, immunities, cover, obstacles, bonuses to saving throws and any cursed techniques.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you spend the maximum amount of CE on Cleave, you can instead create a 5 ft wide, 10 ft long line at a point within 60 ft that you can see. Any creature in range must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure they take maximum damage, on a success they take half as much damage. This damage ignores resistances, immunities, cover, obstacles, bonuses to saving throws and any cursed techniques.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Sky Manipulation -->
	<element name="Cloak of Invisibility" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CLOAK_OF_INVISIBILITY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Sky Shape</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_MANIPULATION_SKY_SHAPE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Sky Shape</em></p>
			<p>As an action, for 3 Cursed Energy you can cast the invisibility spell as the sky surrounds you preventing others from seeing you. When you reach third level, you also gain the benefits of Sky Armor when invisible.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 3 CE, you can cast invisibility</description>
			<description level="3">For 3 CE, you can cast invisibility. While invisible you gain Sky Armor</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_INVISIBILITY" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Spatial Shatter" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SPATIAL_SHATTER">
		<prerequisite>Must have Thin Ice Breaker</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_MANIPULATION_THIN_ICE_BREAKER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Thin Ice Breaker</em></p>
			<p>You can spend 6 CE to make an attack on your turn into a melee cursed energy attack roll using a melee weapon or unarmed strike. On a hit, you deal damage as normal and the target also suffers the effects of Thin Ice Breaker.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 6 CE, make a attack into a melee CE attack using a melee weapon or unarmed strike. On a hit, deal damage as normal and apply Thin Ice Breaker.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Hurricane" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_HURRICANE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Thin Ice Breaker</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SKY_MANIPULATION_THIN_ICE_BREAKER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Thin Ice Breaker</em></p>
			<p>As an action, for 10 Cursed Energy you can spin the space around you forcing all creatures in a 30 foot radius to make a Strength saving throw or be launched 1000 feet into the air as the space rebounds upwards.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 10 CE, creatures in a 30 ft radius must make a Strength save or be launched 1000 ft into the air.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Solo Forbidden Zone -->
	<element name="Blessing of Resilience" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLESSING_OF_RESILIENCE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Bless</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SOLO_FORBIDDEN_ZONE_BLESS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Bless</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered Blessing those within your Zone. Those in your Zone have their output and durability increased. When you create your Zone, all allies in range gain temporary hit points at the start of their turns equal to your Cursed Energy modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Allies in your Zone gain {{ce:modifier}} temporary hit points at the start of their turns.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Blessing of Combat" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLESSING_OF_COMBAT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Ritual Dance</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SOLO_FORBIDDEN_ZONE_RITUAL_DANCE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Ritual Dance</em></p>
			<p>When you use Forbidden Zone, you maximize a creature's output offensively. Allies in your Zone can add a d4 to attack and damage rolls.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Allies in your Zone add a d4 to attack and damage rolls.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Shrine of The Gods" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SHRINE_OF_THE_GODS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximize Output</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_SOLO_FORBIDDEN_ZONE_MAXIMIZE_OUTPUT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximize Output</em></p>
			<p>When setting up your Ritual Zone as part of your full turn action, you can spend an additional 3 cursed energy to roll a d10. Instead of you having to maintain your zone each turn, it instead lasts for a number of rounds equal to the number rolled + your Cursed Energy modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When using Ritual Dance, you can spend an additional 3 CE to roll a d10. The Zone instead lasts that many rounds + {{ce:modifier}} without maintenance.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Star Dictator -->
	<element name="Domineering Shikigami" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_DOMINEERING_SHIKIGAMI">
		<prerequisite>Must have Minor Star Shikigami</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_DICTATOR_MINOR_STAR_SHIKIGAMI</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Minor Star Shikigami</em></p>
			<p>You have learned that strengthening cursed energy lets you summon stronger shikigami. Your Minor Star Shikigami gain the following benefits.</p>
			<ul>
				<li>The Shikigami's Bite attack increases to 1d6. It becomes 1d8 at 6th level and 1d10 at 11th level.</li>
				<li>The Shikigami gains a +2 bonus to their Dexterity score and again at 6th, and 11th level (max of 20).</li>
				<li>When the shikigami is subjected to an effect that allows it to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, it instead takes no damage if it succeeds on the saving throw, and only half damage if it fails.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your Minor Star Shikigami's Bite does 1d6, gains +2 Dex (max of 20), and when it is subjected to an effect that allows it to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, it instead takes no damage if it succeeds on the saving throw, and only half damage if it fails.</description>
			<description level="6">Your Minor Star Shikigami's Bite does 1d8, gains +4 Dex (max of 20), and when it is subjected to an effect that allows it to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, it instead takes no damage if it succeeds on the saving throw, and only half damage if it fails.</description>
			<description level="11">Your Minor Star Shikigami's Bite does 1d10, gains +6 Dex (max of 20), and when it is subjected to an effect that allows it to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, it instead takes no damage if it succeeds on the saving throw, and only half damage if it fails.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Tyrant Shikigami" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TYRANT_SHIKIGAMI">
		<prerequisite>Must have Major Star Shikigami</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_DICTATOR_MAJOR_STAR_SHIKIGAMI</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Major Star Shikigami</em></p>
			<p>You have learned that strengthening cursed energy lets you summon stronger shikigami. You can spend 1 additional cursed energy when you summon your Major Star Shikigami to increase its size category to Large. This increases to 2 cursed energy to make it Huge at 11th level and 4 cursed energy to make it Gargantuan at 18th level. For every size category larger than medium, it gains the following:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>+4 bonus to Strength score</li>
				<li>+1d8 damage to Bite attacks</li>
				<li>+30 hit points</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>You can spend 1 additional CE when you summon your Major Star Shikigami to make it Large. For every size category large than medium it gains a +4 to Strength, +1d8 to Bite, and +30 HP.</description>
			<description level="11">You can spend 1 additional CE when you summon your Major Star Shikigami to make it Large or 2 to make it Huge. For every size category large than medium it gains a +4 to Strength, +1d8 to Bite, and +30 HP.</description>
			<description level="18">You can spend 1 additional CE when you summon your Major Star Shikigami to make it Large, 2 to make it Huge, or 4 to make it Gargantuan. For every size category large than medium it gains a +4 to Strength, +1d8 to Bite, and +30 HP.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Judicial Amputation" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_JUDICIAL_AMPUTATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Army of the Dictator</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_DICTATOR_ARMY_OF_THE_DICTATOR</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Army of the Dictator</em></p>
			<p>If a creature fails their saving throw against your pseudo-domain by 5 or more, the damage is treated as having the Limb Removing Effect and targets one of their arms or legs.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Creatures that fail your pseudo-domain save by 5 or more have the damage do a limb removing effect targeting a arm or leg.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Star Rage -->
	<element name="Massive Push" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MASSIVE_PUSH">
		<prerequisite>Must have Virtual Mass Increase</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_RAGE_VIRTUAL_MASS_INCREASE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Virtual Mass Increase</em></p>
			<p>After landing a critical you can choose to also push the creature 30 feet away. If they hit a solid object or structure, they take the remaining distance as fall damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>On a critical hit, you can push the target 30 ft. If they hit a surface, they take remaining distance as fall damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Shooting Star" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHOOTING_STAR">
		<prerequisite>Must have Virtual Mass Improvement</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_RAGE_VIRTUAL_MASS_IMPROVEMENT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Virtual Mass Improvement</em></p>
			<p>When you have your mass increased, you can spend 3 Cursed Energy once per round to replace one of your attacks by kicking or throwing an object with massive strength. This creates a 5 foot wide, 60 feet long line, causing all creatures within range to make a Dexterity saving throw, taking twice your unarmed strike damage on a failed save as well as targeting a limb from the limb damage table.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you have your mass increased, you can spend 3 CE once per round to replace one of your attacks with a 5 foot wide, 60 feet long line, causing all creatures within range to make a Dexterity saving throw, taking twice your unarmed strike damage on a failed save as well as targeting a limb from the limb damage table.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Black Hole" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BLACK_HOLE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Virtual Mass Mastery</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STAR_RAGE_VIRTUAL_MASS_MASTERY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Virtual Mass Mastery</em></p>
			<p>As an action you can sacrifice yourself, becoming a Black Hole for 1 minute, after which you die. This creates a 100 foot radius of difficult terrain where all creatures within range make a Strength saving throw at the end of your turn, being pulled 50 feet closer on a failed save or 25 feet on a success. If a creature or object gets within 5 feet of you, they are sucked into the black hole and die.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>You become a Black Hole for 1 minute, creating a 100 ft radius of difficult terrain and forcing all creatures within range to make a Strength save at the end of your turn, being pulled 50 ft closer on a failure or 25 ft on a success. Creatures or objects within 5 ft of you die. After the minute you die.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Straw Doll Technique -->
	<element name="Nail Volley" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_NAIL_VOLLEY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Nail Projectile</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STRAW_DOLL_NAIL_PROJECTILE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Nail Projectile</em></p>
			<p>As an action, for as much Cursed Energy as nails you unleash your nails in a cone equal to ten times the nails used you can force creatures in the area to do a Dexterity save or take a number of d6 equal to the nails used.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>Spend any amount of CE to create a (10 ft per CE) cone which forces creatures in the area to make a Dex save or take 1d6 piercing damage per CE used.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="1000 Needles" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_1000_NEEDLES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Hair Pin</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STRAW_DOLL_HAIR_PIN</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Hair Pin</em></p>
			<p>When you use Hairpin, you can spend an additional 1 cursed energy per nail. If the creature fails its saves, it becomes Restrained by needles of cursed energy. An affected creature can make a Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check against your cursed energy save at the end of their turn, freeing themselves on a success. On a failure, they take 1d8 piercing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you release your nails with Hairpin, you can spend an additional 1 CE per nail making them restrain creatures if they fail the Dex save. An affected creature can make a Athletics or Acrobatics check against your CE save DC at the end of their turn, freeing themselves on a success. On a failure, they take 1d8 piercing damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Last Nail in the Coffin" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_LAST_NAIL_IN_THE_COFFIN">
		<prerequisite>Must have Improved Resonance</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_STRAW_DOLL_IMPROVED_RESONANCE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Improved Resonance</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered the Straw Doll Technique, when you use your action to damage a straw doll with Resonance, for 8 Cursed Energy you can choose to land an Improved Resonance.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When using Resonance on a straw doll, you can spend 8 CE to instead apply Improved Resonance.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Technique Extermination -->
	<element name="Blessed Blow" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_BLESSED_BLOW">
		<prerequisite>Must have Extinguishment</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TECHNIQUE_EXTERMINATION_EXTINGUISHMENT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Extinguishment</em></p>
			<p>On a hit you can spend 2 Cursed Energy to deal an additional 2d12 radiant damage. You can increase the damage by 1d12 by spending an additional Cursed Energy. You can only spend as much cursed energy as your Cursed Energy modifier using this feature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>On a hit, spend 2 CE to deal additional 2d12 radiant damage. Spend up to {{ce:modifier}} extra CE to do extra 1d12 per CE spent.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Archangel's Present" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_ARCHANGELS_PRESENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Angel's Blessing, Breakthrough</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TECHNIQUE_EXTERMINATION_ANGELS_BLESSING,[breakthrough:points:1]</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Angel's Blessing, Breakthrough</em></p>
			<p>You gain a Blessing from the Dungeon Master's Guide (In Supernatural Gifts).</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
	</element>

	<element name="Sword of Michael" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SWORD_OF_MICHAEL">
		<prerequisite>Must have Maximum: Jacob's Ladder</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TECHNIQUE_EXTERMINATION_MAXIMUM_JACOBS_LADDER</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Maximum: Jacob's Ladder</em></p>
			<p>Through rigorous effort and control, you have managed to convince the might of Jacob's Ladder into a single blow. As an action for 8 Cursed Energy, you can make a melee Cursed Energy attack against a single creature. On a hit that creature will then suffer the full effects of Jacob's Ladder without a saving throw.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 8 CE, make a melee CE attack. On a hit, the target suffers the full effects of Jacob's Ladder effects with no save.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Teleportation -->
	<element name="Perfected Teleport" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PERFECTED_TELEPORT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Mastered Teleport</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TELEPORTATION_MASTERED_TELEPORT</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Mastered Teleport</em></p>
			<p>You're grown more efficient with your teleports and have perfected their usage. The cost to use your technique instead becomes 1 CE and the cost to cast Teleport is reduced by your CE modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
	</element>

	<element name="Unlimited Marking Works" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_UNLIMITED_MARKING_WORKS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Improved Marking</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TELEPORTATION_IMPROVED_MARKING</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Improved Marking</em></p>
			<p>You have learned a trick to empower your marks. You can now have a number of marks equal to five times your CE modifier. Additionally, your marks last indefinitely.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your marks last indefinitely.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="teleportation:marks:max" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="teleportation:marks:max" value="ce:modifier" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Soul Swap" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_SOUL_SWAP">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Crossroads of Instance</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TELEPORTATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_CROSSROADS_OF_INSTANCE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Crossroads of Instance</em></p>
			<p>With some creative thinking you've figured out an entirely brand new way to use your technique, swapping the souls of creatures. As an action with two willing creatures within 15 feet of you, you can swap the souls of the creatures. For 1 hour or until you dismiss it at will (no action required), all of the creatures' game statistics are swapped except for their mental stats (Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma) and any non-Physical feats if they had one. However, they lose access to their innate technique features and gain access to the other's technique. They also gain the other's cursed energy, hit points, racial features, and weapon proficiencies.</p>
			<p class="indent">When the swap ends both creatures are returned to their original bodies, reverting the changes to game statistics, but each creature can ignore one prerequisite of any feats the other creature used while in their body, except for prerequisites that require you to be or not be a certain race, prerequisites that require you to have a certain cursed technique, prerequisites that require other feats, prerequisites that require a breakthrough, or prerequisites that require you to be a certain class. A creature can only be swapped twice in a one month timeframe, after which you must wait one month before swapping that creature again. If a creature dies while swapped, the other dies once the duration ends.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action">
			<description>Swap the souls of two willing creatures within 15 ft of you. For 1 hour or until you dismiss it at will, all of the creatures' game statistics are swapped except for their mental stats and any non-Physical feats. When the swap ends both creatures are returned to their original bodies, reverting the changes to game statistics, but each creature can ignore one prerequisite of any feats the other creature used while in their body except for ones that require you to be or not be a certain race, have a certain cursed technique, have other feats, have a breakthrough, or be a certain class. A creature can only be swapped twice in a one month timeframe, after which you must wait one month before swapping that creature again. If a creature dies while swapped, the other dies once the duration ends.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Ten Shadows -->
	<element name="Shadow User" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHADOW_USER1">
		<prerequisite>Must have Divine Dogs</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TEN_SHADOWS_DIVINE_DOGS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Divine Dogs</em></p>
			<p>You have furthered your use of shadows. Choose one of the following features (This feat can be taken multiple times).</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Shadow Skulker.</strong> As an action for 2 CE you physically enter the shadows gaining full cover for a turn or until you exit from a shadow within 10 feet. At the start of your turn, you can spend 1 CE to remain in the shadow. You can hear and see through the shadow and can summon tamed shikigami within the shadow. If the shadow is sufficiently illuminated, you exit the shadow.</li>
				<li><strong>Shadow Ridge.</strong> As a reaction for 1 CE against a melee attack, you force a creature within 10 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure the target rolls the attack at disadvantage as their legs fall into their shadow briefly and they fall prone. You can instead spend 3 CE to give the target disadvantage on the save.</li>
				<li><strong>Shadow Spells.</strong> Two shadow spells below 5th level. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Shadow User" supports="Shadow User" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Shadow User" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHADOW_USER2">
		<prerequisite>Must have Divine Dogs</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_FEAT_SHADOW_USER1</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Divine Dogs</em></p>
			<p>You have furthered your use of shadows. Choose one of the following features (This feat can be taken multiple times).</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>Shadow Skulker.</strong> As an action for 2 CE you physically enter the shadows gaining full cover for a turn or until you exit from a shadow within 10 feet. At the start of your turn, you can spend 1 CE to remain in the shadow. You can hear and see through the shadow and can summon tamed shikigami within the shadow. If the shadow is sufficiently illuminated, you exit the shadow.</li>
				<li><strong>Shadow Ridge.</strong> As a reaction for 1 CE against a melee attack, you force a creature within 10 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure the target rolls the attack at disadvantage as their legs fall into their shadow briefly and they fall prone. You can instead spend 3 CE to give the target disadvantage on the save.</li>
				<li><strong>Shadow Spells.</strong> Two shadow spells below 5th level. The CE cost equals the spell's level.</li>
			</ul>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<rules>
			<select type="Feat Feature" name="Shadow User" supports="Shadow User" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Shadow Skulker" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHADOW_SKULKER">
		<supports>Shadow User</supports>
		<description>
			<p><strong>Shadow Skulker.</strong> As an action for 2 CE you physically enter the shadows gaining full cover for a turn or until you exit from a shadow within 10 feet. At the start of your turn, you can spend 1 CE to remain in the shadow. You can hear and see through the shadow and can summon tamed shikigami within the shadow. If the shadow is sufficiently illuminated, you exit the shadow.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 CE, enter the shadows gaining full cover for a turn or until you exit from a shadow within 10 ft. At the start of your turn, you can spend 1 CE to remain in the shadow. You can hear and see through the shadow and can summon tamed shikigami within the shadow. If the shadow is sufficiently illuminated, you exit the shadow.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Shadow Ridge" type="Feat Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_SHADOW_RIDGE">
		<supports>Shadow User</supports>
		<description>
			<p><strong>Shadow Ridge.</strong> As a reaction for 1 CE against a melee attack, you force a creature within 10 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure the target rolls the attack at disadvantage as their legs fall into their shadow briefly and they fall prone. You can instead spend 3 CE to give the target disadvantage on the save.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="CE">
			<description>For 1 CE against a melee attack, force a creature within 10 ft to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure the target rolls the attack at disadvantage and they fall prone. You can instead spend 3 CE to give the target disadvantage on the save.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Chimerafication" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_CHIMERAFICATION">
		<prerequisite>Must have Totality</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TEN_SHADOWS_TOTALITY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Totality</em></p>
			<p>You have learned how to better fuse the powers of your Shadows even at the cost of creating a monstrosity. When creating a Totality, you can sacrifice a tamed shikigami even if it is not destroyed. You can use a number of shikigami up to half your proficiency bonus (rounded up) + 1 that are eligible for Totality to fuse into an eligible Non-Totality shikigami, forming a Chimera. Chimeras can have humanoid forms, but cannot be used for Well's Unknown Abyss.</p>
			<p>You can also give an additional alteration to your altered shikigami created with Well's Unknown Abyss, counting as part of the technique.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Shikigamis created with Well's Unknown Abyss gain an additional alteration. Additionaly, when creating a Totality, you can sacrifice a tamed shikigami even if it is not destroyed. You can use {{ten:shadows:chimera:max}} shikigami that are eligible for Totality to fuse into an eligible Non-Totality shikigami, forming a Chimera. Chimeras can have humanoid forms, but cannot be used for Well's Unknown Abyss.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="ten:shadows:chimera:max" value="proficiency:half:up" />
			<stat name="ten:shadows:chimera:max" value="1" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Embodiment" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_EMBODIMENT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Domain Expansion: Chimera Shadow Garden</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TEN_SHADOWS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_CHIMERA_SHADOW_GARDEN</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Domain Expansion: Chimera Shadow Garden</em></p>
			<p>As an action, you can spend half the cost of one of your tamed shikigami (min of 1). Rather than summoning, you instead gain their movement, actions, legendary actions, features and one ability score of your choice from the shikigami for 1 hour. (Eg. Divine Dog's movement, Max Elephant's Constitution, or Mahoraga's Adaption.) You can embody one shikigami at a time.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>Spend half a tamed shikigami's cost (min of 1) to gain its movement, actions, features, and one ability score for 1 hour (one at a time). You can embody one shikigami at a time.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Tool Manipulation -->
	<element name="Tools of the Craft" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TOOLS_OF_THE_CRAFT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Guided Control</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TOOL_MANIPULATION_GUIDED_CONTROL</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Guided Control</em></p>
			<p>You can imbue a set of tools with your cursed energy, such as artisan's tools or thieve's tools. You can use your CE modifier for ability checks made using these tools and gain a +1 bonus for each CE spent on the imbuement up to a maximum of your CE modifier.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>You can imbue tools to add {{ce:modifier}} for ability check made using these tools adding +1 for each CE spent up to {{ce:modifier}}.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Eyes in the Skies" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_EYES_IN_THE_SKIES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Wind Scythe</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TOOL_MANIPULATION_WIND_SCYTHE</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Wind Scythe</em></p>
			<p>When you are riding your Floating Tool, you gain a +5 bonus to your passive Perception and Investigation and can use your CE modifier for Dexterity saving throws.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>While riding your Floating Tool, gain +5 to passive Perception and Investigation and can use your CE modifier for Dex saves.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Tsukumogami" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_TSUKUMOGAMI">
		<prerequisite>Must have Tool Mastery</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TOOL_MANIPULATION_TOOL_MASTERY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Tool Mastery</em></p>
			<p>As an action for 8 CE, you can imbue a cursed tool with sentience, causing it to come to life and become a Tsukumogami for 1 hour. Your Tsukumogami is always under the effects of Floating Tool and can freely move by itself. It does not count against the number of Floating Tools you can have at once, but you can only have one Tsukumogami at a time.</p>
			<p class="indent">The Tsukumogami can take an action on your turn while you are holding it. That action can be used only to take the Attack action (one weapon attack only), Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object action. If you use Wind Scythe or Combat Tool Improvement's reaction with your Tsukumogami, you can roll three additional dice.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 8 CE, animate a tool into a Tsukumogami for 1 hour which is always under the effects of Floating Tool and can freely move by itself. It does not count against the number of Floating Tools you can have at once, but you can only have one Tsukumogami at a time. It can take an Attack (one weapon attack only), Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object action on your turn while you are holding it. If you use Wind Scythe or Comvat Tool Improvement's reaction with it, you can roll 3 additional dice.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!-- Triple Core -->
	<element name="Maximum: Crippling Strikes" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_CRIPPLING_STRIKES">
		<prerequisite>Must have Unblockable Blows</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRIPLE_CORE_UNBLOCKABLE_BLOWS</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Unblockable Blows</em></p>
			<p>You have mastered your Unblockable Blows core option. Your blows can now treat immunity as resistance by spending 1 additional CE. You can now spend more than 1 CE in an attack.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>For 1 additional CE, your Unblockable Blows treats immunity as resistance.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Blast Away" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BLAST_AWAY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Energy Blast</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRIPLE_CORE_ENERGY_BLAST</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Energy Blast</em></p>
			<p>You have improved your output. When you use your Energy Blast core option with at least 4 CE, the damage dice becomes d8 and creatures must make a Strength saving throw or be knocked 10ft back and fall prone.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use Energy Blast with at least 4 CE, the damage dice becomes d8 and creatures must make a Strength saving throw or be knocked 10ft back and fall prone.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Fortress" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_FORTRESS">
		<prerequisite>Must have Defensive Form</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRIPLE_CORE_DEFENSIVE_FORM</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Defensive Form</em></p>
			<p>When you use your Defensive Form core option, you instead gain temporary hit points equal to four times your current CE. While you have these temporary hit points, you are resistant to Piercing, Bludgeoning, and Slashing damage.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use Defensive Form instead gain 4x your current CE in temp HP and while you have them you are resistant to Piercing, Bludgeoning, and Slashing damage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Maximum: Blitz" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_MAXIMUM_BLITZ">
		<prerequisite>Must have Divebomb</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_TRIPLE_CORE_DIVEBOMB</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Divebomb</em></p>
			<p>You have hastened yourself even further. When you use your Divebomb core option, you instead increase your speed by 15 ft per CE spent and you gain a +4 bonus to AC. You deal an additional 1d6 damage for every 10 ft you move in a straight line before hitting a target with a melee attack.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you use Divebomb you instead increase your speed by 15 ft per CE spent and gain a +4 bonus to AC. You deal an additional 1d6 damage for every 10 ft you move in a straight line before hitting a target with a melee attack.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="triple:core:divebomb:speed" value="5" />
			<stat name="triple:core:divebomb:ac" value="2" />
			<stat name="triple:core:divebomb:damage" value="2" />
			<stat name="triple:core:divebomb:distance" value="-5" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Vengeful Spirit Manipulation -->
	<element name="Partial Manifestation Versatility" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_PARTIAL_MANIFESTATION_VERSATILITY">
		<prerequisite>Must have Partial Manifestation</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VENGEFUL_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_PARTIAL_MANIFESTATION</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Partial Manifestation</em></p>
			<p>Your manipulation over the manifestation of limbs and such increase. The range of your partial manifestation attacks increases to 15 ft. Additionally, when you hit with one of these attacks, you can attempt to grapple or shove the target as part of the attack.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Partial Manifestation attacks have 15 ft range and can grapple or shove on a hit as part of the attack.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Technique Storage" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_TECHNIQUE_STORAGE">
		<prerequisite>Must have Mimicry</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VENGEFUL_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_MIMICRY</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Mimicry</em></p>
			<p>When you copy techniques, you can keep more in the Vengeful Spirit. You can store twice as many techniques, with any additional techniques being stored within your spirit. You must use an action to retrieve them while within 5 ft of the Vengeful Spirit while it is summoned.</p>
			<p>While your Vengeful Spirit is summoned, the number of times you can use a copied technique feature before it disappears increases by your CE modifier. The increased number of uses does not reset when your Vengeful Spirit is resummoned.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can store {{ce:modifier}} more techniques, with any additional techniques being stored within your spirit. You must use an action to retrieve them while within 5 ft of the Vengeful Spirit while it is summoned. While your Vengeful Spirit is summoned, the number of times you can use a copied technique feature before it disappears increases by {{ce:modifier}}. The increased number of uses does not reset when your Vengeful Spirit is resummoned.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Free Spirit" type="Feat" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_FEAT_FREE_SPIRIT">
		<prerequisite>Must have Stronger Bond</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_VENGEFUL_SPIRIT_MANIPULATION_STRONGER_BOND</requirements>
		<supports>Innate Technique Feats</supports>
		<description>
			<p><em>Prerequisite: Must have Stronger Bond</em></p>
			<p>You and your spirit have finally made amends, making it finally pass on to the afterlife. However, the spirit left you a present before going. Your Vengeful Spirit is now fully under your control, not being berserk when you summon it. It is now a Shikigami instead of a Cursed Spirit. Although you can use your action to give it an order, making it act on its own to complete the order. While summoned, you can use your action to borrow its power, drawing cursed energy equal to your level into yourself from its pool once per day. The spirit can only be active for a number of minutes equal to your CE modifier per day.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Your Vengeful Spirit is now fully under your control, not being berserk when you summon it. It is now a Shikigami instead of a Cursed Spirit. You can use your action to give it an order, making it act on its own to complete the order. While summoned, you can use your action to draw {{level}} CE from its pool once per day. The spirit can only be active for {{ce:modifier}} minutes per day.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>
</elements>