<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="6.0.0">
			<file name="g-warstaff.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innate-techniques(archetypes)/g-warstaff.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="G Warstaff" type="Archetype" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_G_WARSTAFF">
		<supports>Innate Technique</supports>
		<description>
			<p>You have manga on your mind.</p>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_WARSTAFF" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_HIGHLIGHTED_PANELS" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION" />
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>You can conjure a pen-like cursed tool that lets you see the future.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_WARSTAFF" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_HIGHLIGHTED_PANELS" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Warstaff" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_WARSTAFF">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_WARSTAFF</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Starting at 1st level, you can summon a pen-like cursed tool that allows you to see into the future of your opponents. As a bonus action for 2 cursed energy, you create an oversized pen-like cursed tool. This cursed tool has the reach and two-handed properties and you can use your CE modifier for its attack and damage rolls. On a hit it deals 1d4 + your CE modifier piercing damage and counts as a grade 4 cursed tool and can be used with martial arts die. You can dismiss the Warstaff at will and can only have one created at a time.</p>
            <p> When you hit a creature with G Warstaff, you fulfill the condition for ink and attach a manga panel to the target, being able to view 1 second into the target's future. Hitting a target more than once adds another 1 second to the total, making you gain the benefits of the earlier seconds and the current. As a reaction or bonus action for 1 cursed energy, you can view that creature's future again and gain the following foresights until the beginning of your next turn depending on the creature's marks. You cannot use this while blinded.</p>
            <h5 class="caption">FORESIGHTS</h5>
				<table>
                	<thead>
                    	<tr><td>Seconds</td><td>Foresight</td></tr>
                	</thead>
                	<tr><td>1 Second</td><td>The creature's attack rolls against you are made at disadvantage</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>2 Seconds</td><td>You have advantage on saving throws from that creature</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>3 Seconds</td><td>You have advantage on attack rolls against that creature</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>4 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the start of their turn)</td></tr>
               	 	<tr><td>5 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the end of your turn)</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>6 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the beginning of your turn)</td></tr>
            	</table>
            <p>You can only see into a number of seconds into a creature's future equal to your proficiency bonus. The number of creatures that can be affected by this technique is equal to your CE modifier, and you can end the technique at will or it ends when the combat ends.</p>
        </description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2 cursed energy, you create an oversized pen-like cursed tool. This cursed tool has the reach and two-handed properties and you can use your CE modifier for its attack and damage rolls. On a hit it deals 1d4 + {{ce:modifier}} piercing damage and counts as a grade 4 cursed tool and can be used with martial arts die. You can dismiss the Warstaff at will and can only have one created at a time. Hitting a target adds 1 second to the creature. As a reaction or bonus action for 1 cursed energy, you gain the foresights until the beginning of your next turn depending on the creature's marks. You cannot use this while blinded. You can only see {{proficiency}} seconds into a creature's future. You can affect {{ce:modifier}} creatures with this technique, and you can end the technique at will or it ends when the combat ends.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_FORESIGHT" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Foresight" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_FORESIGHT">
		<description> 
		<h5 class="caption">FORESIGHTS</h5>
				<table>
                	<thead>
                    	<tr><td>Seconds</td><td>Foresight</td></tr>
                	</thead>
                	<tr><td>1 Second</td><td>The creature's attack rolls against you are made at disadvantage</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>2 Seconds</td><td>You have advantage on saving throws from that creature</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>3 Seconds</td><td>You have advantage on attack rolls against that creature</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>4 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the start of their turn)</td></tr>
               	 	<tr><td>5 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the end of your turn)</td></tr>
                	<tr><td>6 Seconds</td><td>You know the next actions of the creature (The DM tells you at the beginning of your turn)</td></tr>
            	</table>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>At 1 second, the creature's attack rolls against you are made at disadvantage. At 2 seconds, you have advantage on saving throws from that creature. At 3 seconds, you have advantage on attack rolls against that creature. At 4, 5, or 6 seconds the DM tells you the next actions of the creature at the start of their turn, end of your turn, or beginning of your turn</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>
	
	<element name="Highlighted Panels" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_HIGHLIGHTED_PANELS">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_HIGHLIGHTED_PANELS</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 3rd level, with the power of reading into the future, no one surprises you anymore. As long as you can see 2 seconds into a creature's future, you take half damage on a failure, and no damage on a success against saving throws caused by that creature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>As long as you can see 2 seconds into a creature's future, you take half damage on a failure, and no damage on a success against saving throws caused by that creature.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Predictable Strikes" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 6th level, your opponents become extremely easy to read after being affected by your technique, and you learned how to exploit that. Once per turn when you hit an attack using G Warstaff against a creature that you can see 3 seconds into the future, you can turn that attack into a critical. You cannot roll for a black flash using this feature.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet usage="1/Turn">
            <description>When you hit an attack using G Warstaff against a creature that you can see 3 seconds into the future, you can turn that attack into a critical. You cannot roll for a black flash using this feature.</description>
        </sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Precognition" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 11th level, you can glimpse your own future, knowing exactly what to do and when. When you roll with advantage against a creature because of your technique, your critical range is increased by half your CE modifier(rounded down).</p>
            <p class="indent">Whenever a creature rolls with disadvantage against you because of your technique, the roll's critical fail range is increased by half of your CE modifier(rounded down). For example, if you have a +4 CE modifier and they roll a natural 3 on their roll, it counts as a critical failure.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>When you roll with advantage against a creature because of your technique, your critical range is increased by {{ce:modifier}}/2 rounded down. Whenever a creature rolls with disadvantage against you because of your technique, the roll's critical fail range is increased by {{ce:modifier}}/2 rounded down. </description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Domain Expansion: Storyboard Dominion" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 18th level, you have mastered your technique allowing you to expand your domain. All creatures in your domain count as having 6 seconds marked and at initiative 20, you can see 6 seconds into the future of all creatures.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>All creatures in your domain count as having 6 seconds marked. At initiative 20, you can see 6 seconds into the future of all creatures.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_JJK_CLASS_FEATURE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION">
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Warstaff Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_WARSTAFF" />
	<element name="Highlighted Panels Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_HIGHLIGHTED_PANELS" />
	<element name="Predictable Strikes Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_PREDICTABLE_STRIKES" />
	<element name="Precognition Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_PRECOGNITION" />
	<element name="Domain Expansion: Storyboard Dominion Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_G_WARSTAFF_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_STORYBOARD_DOMINION" />
</elements>
