<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="6.0.1">
			<file name="hair-manipulation.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innate-techniques(archetypes)/hair-manipulation.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="Hair Manipulation" type="Archetype" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_HAIR_MANIPULATION">
		<supports>Innate Technique</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Your technique allows you to form your hair into a variety of shapes.</p>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HAIR_SPRAY" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SILKEN_STRAND_EXECUTION_GROUND" />
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>Your technique allows you to form your hair into a variety of shapes.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HAIR_SPRAY" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SILKEN_STRAND_EXECUTION_GROUND" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Scorpion Hair" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Beginning at 1st level, you have learned to move your hair into different forms using cursed energy. When you take the Attack action, you can spend 1 CE to replace an attack by shaping your hair into a barbed stinger. Make a melee cursed energy attack against a creature within 10 ft of you. On a hit you deal 1d10 + your CE modifier piercing damage. You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls with this attack at 3rd level. This increases to a +2 bonus at 6th level, +3 bonus at 11th level and +4 bonus at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you take the Attack action, you can spend 1 CE to replace an attack by shaping your hair into a barbed stinger. Make a melee CE attack against a creature within 10 ft of you. On a hit you deal 1d10 + {{hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:damage}} piercing damage.</description>
			<description level="3">When you take the Attack action, you can spend 1 CE to replace an attack by shaping your hair into a barbed stinger. Make a melee CE attack with a +{{hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus}} to hit against a creature within 10 ft of you. On a hit you deal 1d10 + {{hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:damage}} piercing damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus" value="1" level="3" bonus="scorpion hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus" value="2" level="6" bonus="scorpion hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus" value="3" level="11" bonus="scorpion hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus" value="4" level="18" bonus="scorpion hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:damage" value="ce:modifier" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:damage" value="hair:manipulation:scorpion:hair:bonus" level="3" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Drill Hair" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 3rd level, you have learned to form your hair into drill bits and shoot them off as projectiles. When you take the Attack action, you can spend 1 cursed energy to replace an attack with a ranged cursed energy attack roll with a range of 30ft. This attack deals 1d6 + your CE modifier piercing damage. The range of this technique increases to 60 ft at 6th level.</p>
			<p class="indent">When attacking with a drill, you can spend an additional 2 cursed energy to make the drill explode in a 5 ft radius upon the point of impact causing creatures in range to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they take an additional 3d6 fire damage. On a success, they take half as much damage. The fire damage increases to 5d6 at 6th level, 8d6 at 11th level and 10d6 at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="CE">
			<description>When you take the Attack action, you can spend 1 CE to replace an attack with a ranged CE attack roll with a range of {{hair:manipulation:drill:hair:distance}}ft. This attack deals 1d6 + {{ce:modifier}} piercing damage. You can spend an additional 2 CE to make the drill explode in a 5 ft radius upon the point of impact causing creatures in range to make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, they take an additional {{hair:manipulation:drill:hair:damage}}d6 fire damage. On a success, they take half as much damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:distance" value="30" bonus="drill hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:distance" value="60" bonus="drill hair" level="6" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:damage" value="3" bonus="drill hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:damage" value="5" bonus="drill hair" level="6" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:damage" value="8" bonus="drill hair" level="11" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:drill:hair:damage" value="10" bonus="drill hair" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Aircraft Hair" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 6th level you have learned to make more complex constructs from your hair. As an action for 3 CE, you form your hair into either a Jet or Helicopter for 1 minute and can spend 1 CE to keep the form active for 1 minute:</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Helicopter Hair.</strong> You gain a flying speed equal to your walking speed and can take the Dash action as a bonus action. When you take the attack action, you can spend 2 cursed energy to replace one attack by extending your blades and attempting to slash an enemy. Make a melee cursed energy attack, on a hit you deal 6d8 + your CE modifier slashing damage. This damage increases to 8d8 at 11th level, and 10d8 at 18th level.</p>
			<p class="indent">A creature that hits you with an Opportunity attack takes slashing damage equal to your CE modifier. This becomes twice your CE modifier at 11th level.</p>
			<p class="indent"><strong>Jet Hair.</strong> You gain a flying speed equal to your walking speed. When you take the dash action while flying, you not only do not provoke opportunity attacks, but can also choose to move in a straight line and crash through creatures. All creatures in your path must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take Xd8 bludgeoning damage and are pushed back 30 ft away from you and knocked prone. If they impact a solid surface, they take 1d4 bludgeoning for every 10 ft you traveled in a straight line before crashing into them. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed or knocked prone. (X = CE modifier)</p>
			<p class="indent">At 11th level, taking the Dash action while flying you instead move up to twice your flying speed. This increases to three times your flying speed at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
            <description>For 3 CE, form your hair into either a Jet or Helicopter for 1 minute and you can spend 1 CE to keep the form active for a additional minute.</description>
        </sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HELICOPTER_HAIR" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_JET_HAIR" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Helicopter Hair" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HELICOPTER_HAIR">
		<description>
			<p>You gain a flying speed equal to your walking speed and can take the Dash action as a bonus action. When you take the attack action, you can spend 2 cursed energy to replace one attack by extending your blades and attempting to slash an enemy. Make a melee cursed energy attack, on a hit you deal 6d8 + your CE modifier slashing damage. This damage increases to 8d8 at 11th level, and 10d8 at 18th level.</p>
			<p class="indent">A creature that hits you with an Opportunity attack takes slashing damage equal to your CE modifier. This becomes twice your CE modifier at 11th level.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You gain a {{speed}} ft. flying speed and can take the Dash action as a bonus action. When you take the attack action, you can spend 2 CE to replace one attack with a melee CE attack. On a hit you deal {{hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:damage}}d8 + {{ce:modifier}} slashing damage. A creature that hits you with an opportunity attack takes {{hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:opportunity}} slashing damage.</description>
        </sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:damage" value="6" bonus="helicopter hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:damage" value="8" bonus="helicopter hair" level="11" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:damage" value="10" bonus="helicopter hair" level="18" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:opportunity" value="ce:modifier" bonus="helicopter hair" />
			<stat name="hair:manipulation:helicopter:hair:opportunity" value="ce:modifier" bonus="helicopter hair" level="11" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Jet Hair" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_JET_HAIR">
		<description>
			<p>You gain a flying speed equal to your walking speed. When you take the dash action while flying, you not only do not provoke opportunity attacks, but can also choose to move in a straight line and crash through creatures. All creatures in your path must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take Xd8 bludgeoning damage and are pushed back 30 ft away from you and knocked prone. If they impact a solid surface, they take 1d4 bludgeoning for every 10 ft you traveled in a straight line before crashing into them. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed or knocked prone. (X = CE modifier)</p>
			<p class="indent">At 11th level, taking the Dash action while flying you instead move up to twice your flying speed. This increases to three times your flying speed at 18th level.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You gain a {{speed}} ft. flying speed. When you take the dash action while flying you do not provoke opportunity attacks and can move in a straight line to crash through creatures. All creatures in your path must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take {{ce:modifier}}d8 bludgeoning damage and are pushed back 30 ft away from you and knocked prone. If they impact a solid surface, they take 1d4 bludgeoning for every 10 ft you traveled in a straight line before crashing into them. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed or knocked prone.</description>
			<description level="11">You gain a {{speed}} ft. flying speed. When you take the dash action you can move a extra two times your flying speed instead of one. of while flying you do not provoke opportunity attacks and can move in a straight line to crash through creatures. All creatures in your path must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take {{ce:modifier}}d8 bludgeoning damage and are pushed back 30 ft away from you and knocked prone. If they impact a solid surface, they take 1d4 bludgeoning for every 10 ft you traveled in a straight line before crashing into them. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed or knocked prone.</description>
			<description level="18">You gain a {{speed}} ft. flying speed. When you take the dash action you can move a extra three times your flying speed instead of one. of while flying you do not provoke opportunity attacks and can move in a straight line to crash through creatures. All creatures in your path must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, they take {{ce:modifier}}d8 bludgeoning damage and are pushed back 30 ft away from you and knocked prone. If they impact a solid surface, they take 1d4 bludgeoning for every 10 ft you traveled in a straight line before crashing into them. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed or knocked prone.</description>
        </sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Hair Spray" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HAIR_SPRAY">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HAIR_SPRAY</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 11th level, your hair has become almost indestructible, allowing you to grow it to longer lengths and activate your techniques more freely. The melee reach of your techniques increases by 5 ft and your hair counts as a Grade 1 Cursed Tool. At 18th level, your hair counts as a Special Grade Cursed Tool.</p>
			<p class="indent">Once per turn you can spend 2 additional CE to activate one of your technique features requiring an attack roll as a bonus action. An attack roll made using this special free action is made at advantage. Alternatively, once per turn you can spend 4 CE to activate one of your technique features requiring a saving throw as a bonus action. A saving throw forced by this special free action is made at disadvantage.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet usage="CE">
			<description>The melee reach of your techniques increases by 5 ft and your hair counts as a Grade 1 Cursed Tool. Once per turn you can spend 2 additional CE to activate one of your technique features requiring an attack roll as a bonus action. An attack roll made using this is made at advantage. Alternatively, once per turn you can spend 4 CE to activate one of your technique features requiring a saving throw as a bonus action. A saving throw forced by this special free action is made at disadvantage.</description>
			<description level="18">The melee reach of your techniques increases by 5 ft and your hair counts as a Special Grade Cursed Tool. Once per turn you can spend 2 additional CE to activate one of your technique features requiring an attack roll as a bonus action. An attack roll made using this is made at advantage. Alternatively, once per turn you can spend 4 CE to activate one of your technique features requiring a saving throw as a bonus action. A saving throw forced by this special free action is made at disadvantage.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Domain Expansion: Silken Strand Execution Ground" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SILKEN_STRAND_EXECUTION_GROUND">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SILKEN_STRAND_EXECUTION_GROUND</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Finally at 18th level you have learned to expand your domain. Creatures other than you take 2d10 slashing damage for every 5 ft they move within your domain as infinitesimally small and sharp hairs cut into them with their every movement. Your domain counts as difficult terrain for creatures other than you.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>Creatures other than you take 2d10 slashing damage for every 5 ft they move. Your domain counts as difficult terrain for creatures other than you.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_JJK_CLASS_FEATURE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION"/>
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Scorpion Hair Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_SCORPION_HAIR" />
	<element name="Drill Hair Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DRILL_HAIR" />
	<element name="Aircraft Hair Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_AIRCRAFT_HAIR" />
	<element name="Hair Spray Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_HAIR_SPRAY" />
	<element name="Domain Expansion: Silken Strand Execution Ground Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_HAIR_MANIPULATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SILKEN_STRAND_EXECUTION_GROUND" />
</elements>
