<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="6.0.0">
			<file name="idle-transfiguration.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innate-techniques(archetypes)/idle-transfiguration.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="Idle Transfiguration" type="Archetype" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION">
		<supports>Innate Technique</supports>
		<description>
			<p>The diddy touch.</p>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURATION" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY" />
            <div class="reference">
                <div element="ID_JJK_INFORMATION_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER" />
            </div>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION" />
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>The soul is an interesting thing and your technique manipulates it.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURATION" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Transfiguration" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURATION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURATION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Starting at 1st level, your touch can alter a creature's very own being, their soul. Whenever you hit a creature with a natural weapon, unarmed strike, or touch them, you can deal an additional 1d6 Necrotic damage.</p>
            <p class="indent">In addition, as an action for 1 Cursed Energy, you can force said creature within your reach to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they will take 1d10 Necrotic Damage, which increases to 2d10 at 3rd level, 3d10 at 6th level, 4d10 at 11th level, and 5d10 at 18th level. On a success, the creature takes half as much damage. This damage reduces a creature's hit point maximum until they finish a long rest.</p>
            <p class="indent">If Necrotic damage from any features of your Idle Transfiguration reduces a creature's total hit points to 0, the creature will become one of your Transfigured Creatures. This does not work on Constructs.</p>
            <p class="indent"><strong>Transfigured Creatures.</strong> You can have a number of transfigured creatures equal to your level times your Cursed Energy modifier. Transfigured creatures will follow your orders, act at the end of your turn and their creature type is undead. On a short or long rest, you can modify a transfigured creature's size from tiny to huge.</p>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Ability Scores.</strong> The creature's mental scores will be decreased to 4. You can redistribute the points removed from their mental stats into their physical scores, even beyond 20.</li>
                <li><strong>Primitiveness.</strong> Transformed creatures lose all supernatural abilities like cursed technique as well as proficiencies, and their AC is 10 + Dexterity modifier. They can only use natural weapons or unarmed attacks. They can roll a d6 in place of the normal damage of their unarmed strike.</li>            
            </ul>
            <p class="indent">You can command with simple orders such as to attack a creature as a bonus action. Complex orders like area control are an action. You can store transfigured creatures, extracting any number as a bonus action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>Whenever you hit a creature with a natural weapon, unarmed strike, or touch them, you can deal an additional 1d6 Necrotic damage. As an action for 1 cursed energy, you can force said creature within your reach to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failure, they will take {{idle:transfiguration:damage}}d10 Necrotic Damage which reduces a creature's hit point maximum until they finish a long rest. On a success, the creature takes half as much damage. If Necrotic damage from any features of your Idle Transfiguration reduces a creature's total hit points to 0, the creature will become one of your Transfigured Creatures. This does not work on Constructs.</description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURED_CREATURES" />
            <stat name="idle:transfiguration:damage" value="1" level="1" bonus="transfiguration" />
            <stat name="idle:transfiguration:damage" value="2" level="3" bonus="transfiguration" />
            <stat name="idle:transfiguration:damage" value="3" level="6" bonus="transfiguration" />
            <stat name="idle:transfiguration:damage" value="4" level="11" bonus="transfiguration" />
            <stat name="idle:transfiguration:damage" value="5" level="18" bonus="transfiguration" />
        </rules>
	</element>

    <element name="Transfigured Creatures" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURED_CREATURES">
        <description>
            <p>You can have a number of transfigured creatures equal to your level times your Cursed Energy modifier. Transfigured creatures will follow your orders, act at the end of your turn and their creature type is undead. On a short or long rest, you can modify a transfigured creature's size from tiny to huge.</p>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Ability Scores.</strong> The creature's mental scores will be decreased to 4. You can redistribute the points removed from their mental stats into their physical scores, even beyond 20.</li>
                <li><strong>Primitiveness.</strong> Transformed creatures lose all supernatural abilities like cursed technique as well as proficiencies, and their AC is 10 + Dexterity modifier. They can only use natural weapons or unarmed attacks. They can roll a d6 in place of the normal damage of their unarmed strike.</li>            
            </ul>
            <p>You can command with simple orders such as to attack a creature as a bonus action. Complex orders like area control are an action. You can store transfigured creatures, extracting any number as a bonus action.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You can have {{level}}*{{ce:modifier}} transfigured creatures. Their mental scores decrease to 4 and you can redistribute the points removed from their mental stats into their physical scores, even beyond 20. They lose all abilities and their AC is {{transfigured:creatures:ac}} and can only use natural weapons or unarmed attacks which are d6. Transfigured creatures will follow your orders, act at the end of your turn, and their creature type is undead. On a short or long rest, you can modify a transfigured creature's size from tiny to huge.</description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <stat name="transfigured:creatures:ac" value="10" />
            <stat name="transfigured:creatures:ac" value="dexterity:modifier" />
        </rules>
    </element>

	<element name="Alteration" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Beginning at 3rd level, you can safely alter yourself or an ally.</p>
            <p class="indent"><strong>Ally Alteration:</strong> You can use your alteration on willing creatures, to alter them as you see fit. You alter a willing creature during a short or long rest, granting them one or more of the following benefits:</p>
            <h5 class="caption">ALLY ALTERATIONS</h5>
                <table>
                    <thead>
                        <tr><td>Alteration</td><td>Description</td></tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tr><td>Heightened Smell</td><td>The creature gains advantage in perception checks involving smell.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Heightened Hearing</td><td>The creature gains advantage in perception checks involving hearing.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Heightened Sight</td><td>The creature gains advantage in perception checks involving sight.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Darkvision</td><td>The creature has darkvision with a radius of 60 feet, if the creature already has darkvision it will extend its range by 30 feet.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Hardened Skin</td><td>The creature gains resistance to either: bludgeoning, slashing, or piercing.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Gills</td><td>The creature gains a swimming speed equal to its walking speed and can breathe underwater.</td></tr>
                </table>
            <p class="indent"><strong>Self-Alteration:</strong> You have learned how to shape your own form in many different ways. As a bonus action, you can gain new body parts. You can choose one of the following:</p>
            <h5 class="caption">SELF-ALTERATIONS</h5>
                <table>
                    <thead>
                        <tr><td>Alteration</td><td>CE Cost</td><td>Description</td><td>Restrictions</td></tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tr><td>Sword Arms</td><td>2</td><td>Your unarmed strikes deal slashing and count as light, finesse, martial melee weapons</td><td>No Spike Hands or Wings</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Spike Hands</td><td>2</td><td>Your unarmed strikes deal piercing damage, and increases damage by your Proficiency</td><td>No Sword Arms or Wings</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Arm Shields</td><td>2</td><td>+2 bonus to AC.</td><td>No Wings</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Long Arms</td><td>2</td><td>Increase melee reach by 10 feet</td><td>No Wings</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Horse Hooves</td><td>3</td><td>Increase movement by 10 feet and Bonus Action dash.</td><td>N/A</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Spike Skin</td><td>2</td><td>As a reaction to a melee attack within 5 feet, you can deal Piercing damage equal to 4x your Proficiency.</td><td>N/A</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Wings</td><td>4</td><td>You gain a 60 ft fly speed. While at least 15 feet away, you gain a +2 bonus to AC</td><td>No Spike Hands, Sword Hands, Arm Shield, or Long Arms</td></tr>
                </table>
            <p class="indent">At 6th level, you gain the following Self-Alteration option:</p>
            <p class="indent"><strong>Size Change.</strong> For 2 CE, you increase or decrease your size by 1 category for 1 min (does not stack). While enlarged you have advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws and your unarmed strikes deal 1d4 extra damage. While reduced you have advantage on Dexterity checks and saves and a +1 to AC. You can revert as a bonus action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You can alter a willing creature during a short or long rest. As a bonus action, you can gain new body parts by paying their CE Cost.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Body Clone" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 6th level, you have learned how to create a near perfect clone of yourself. As an action for 6 Cursed Energy, you create a copy of yourself, giving it half of your current and max Hit Points and Cursed Energy. It is identical to you, controlled by you, acts at the end of your turn, and you can view through its senses. Your clone cannot use your Innate Technique features except Self-Alteration. You can't make another clone until it dies or you touch it and rejoin, granting you back the rest of your max HP and Cursed Energy.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
            <description>For 6 cursed energy, you create a copy of yourself, giving it half of your current and max Hit Points and Cursed Energy. It is identical to you, controlled by you, acts at the end of your turn, and you can view through its senses. Your clone cannot use your Innate Technique features except Self-Alteration. You can't make another clone until it dies or you touch it and rejoin, granting you back the rest of your max HP and Cursed Energy.</description>
        </sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Soul Multiplicity" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Starting at 11th level, you can use Self-Alteration as a free action on your turn. As an action for 5 Cursed Energy you can spend 2 or more of your Transfigured Creatures, fusing them together to create one of the following effects:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Body Repel.</strong> You create a barrage of Transfigured creatures being launched at high speeds. You make a ranged Cursed Energy attack with a range of 60/120 feet that deals 4d8 necrotic damage on a hit. For every additional Transfigured Creature, you deal another 1d8 necrotic damage and can split the damage die between different targets to make multiple attacks.</li>
                <li><strong>Polymorphic Soul Isomer.</strong> You create a Polymorphic Soul Isomer for 1 minute. When using this technique, you can add another Transfigured Creature to the fusion. Each Transfigured Creature counts as one soul.</li>
                <div class="reference">
                    <div element="ID_JJK_INFORMATION_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER" />
                </div>
            </ul>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>For 5 cursed energy, you can fuse 2 or more of your Transfigured Creatures to use Body Repel or create a Polymorphic Soul Isomer. </description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY_BODY_REPEL" />
            <grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER" />
			<select type="Companion" name="Polymorphic Soul Isomer" supports="Polymorphic Soul Isomer" />
        </rules>
	</element>

    <element name="Body Repel" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY_BODY_REPEL">
        <description>
            <p>You create a barrage of Transfigured creatures being launched at high speeds. You make a ranged Cursed Energy attack with a range of 60/120 feet that deals 4d8 necrotic damage on a hit. For every additional Transfigured Creature, you deal another 1d8 necrotic damage and can split the damage die between different targets to make multiple attacks.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You make a ranged Cursed Energy attack with a range of 60/120 feet that deals 4d8 necrotic damage on a hit. For every additional Transfigured Creature, you deal another 1d8 necrotic damage and can split the damage die between different targets to make multiple attacks.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

    <element name="Polymorphic Soul Isomer" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER">
        <description>
            <p>You create a Polymorphic Soul Isomer for 1 minute. When using this technique, you can add another Transfigured Creature to the fusion. Each Transfigured Creature counts as one soul.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>You create a Polymorphic Soul Isomer for 1 minute. Each Transfigured Creature counts as one soul.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

	<element name="Domain Expansion: Self-Embodiment of Perfection" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Finally, at 18th level, you have studied your powers and have finally learned your most powerful technique. You create a large dimension filled with your body parts, making escaping death impossible. At initiative 20 creatures within your domain suffer twice your Transfiguration touch damage.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>At initiative 20, creatures within your domain suffer twice your Transfiguration touch damage.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_JJK_CLASS_FEATURE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION"/>
		</rules>
	</element>

    <!-- Companion Reference -->
    <element name="Polymorphic Soul Isomer" type="Information" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_INFORMATION_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER">
        <description>
            <p style="margin-bottom:-5px"><em>Medium undead, unaligned</em></p>
            <h4 style="margin-top:5px"></h4>
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong>Armor Class</strong> 15 (natural armor)</li>
                <li><strong>Hit Points</strong> 100</li>
                <li><strong>Speed</strong> 60 ft.</li>
            </ul>
            <table style="text-align:center;margin-top:10px;margin-bottom:10px">
                <thead>
                    <tr><td>STR</td><td>DEX</td><td>CON</td><td>INT</td><td>WIS</td><td>CHA</td></tr>
                </thead>
                <tr>
                    <td>18 (+4)</td><td>18 (+4)</td><td>18 (+4)</td><td>4 (-3)</td><td>4 (-3)</td><td>4 (-3)</td>
                </tr>
            </table>
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong>Damage Immunities</strong> necrotic</li>
                <li><strong>Condition Immunities</strong> charmed, frightened</li>
                <li><strong>Senses</strong> passive Perception 7</li>
                <li><strong>Languages</strong> —</li>
                <li style="margin-bottom:-1em"><strong>Challenge</strong> N/A</li>
            </ul>
			<h4 style="margin-top:5px; margin-bottom:10px" />
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong><em>Soul Incompatibility.</em></strong> For every 2 additional souls used in its creation, the Isomer gains a +2 to Strength, Dexterity, and Constitution scores and deals additional damage on a hit, but its maximum hit points decrease by 20.</li>
            </ul>

            <h4 style="margin-top:10px">Actions</h4>
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong><em>Multiattack.</em></strong> The Isomer makes two slam attacks.</li>
                <li><em><strong>Slam.</strong> Melee Weapon Attack:</em> (Strength modifier + your proficiency) to hit, reach 5 ft., one target. Hit: 12 (1d12 + STR souls) bludgeoning damage.</li>
            </ul>
        </description>
    </element>

    <!-- Companion -->
    <element name="Polymorphic Soul Isomer" type="Companion" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_COMPANION_POLYMORPHIC_SOUL_ISOMER">
        <supports>Polymorphic Soul Isomer</supports>
        <setters>
            <set name="strength">18</set>
            <set name="dexterity">18</set>
            <set name="constitution">18</set>
            <set name="intelligence">4</set>
            <set name="wisdom">4</set>
            <set name="charisma">4</set>
            <set name="ac">15 (natural armor)</set>
            <set name="hp">100</set>
            <set name="speed">60 ft.</set>
            <set name="senses">passive Perception 7</set>
            <set name="languages">-</set>
            <set name="immunities">necrotic</set>
            <set name="conditionImmunities">charmed, frightened</set>
            <set name="type">Undead</set>
            <set name="size">Medium</set>
            <set name="alignment">unaligned</set>
            <set name="challenge">—</set>
            <set name="traits">ID_JJK_COMPANION_TRAIT_ISOMER_SOUL_INCOMPATIBILITY</set>
            <set name="actions">ID_JJK_COMPANION_ACTION_ISOMER_MULTIATTACK,ID_JJK_COMPANION_ACTION_ISOMER_SLAM</set>
        </setters>
        <rules>
            <stat name="companion:ac" value="15" />
            <stat name="companion:hp:max" value="100" bonus="base" />
            <stat name="companion:speed" value="60" bonus="base" />
        </rules>
    </element>

    <element name="Multiattack" type="Companion Action" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_COMPANION_ACTION_ISOMER_MULTIATTACK">
        <description>
            <p>The Isomer makes two slam attacks.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>The Isomer makes two slam attacks.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>


    <element name="Slam" type="Companion Action" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_COMPANION_ACTION_ISOMER_SLAM">
        <description>
            <p>Melee Weapon Attack: (Strength modifier + your proficiency) to hit, reach 5 ft., one target. Hit: 12 (1d12 + STR + souls) bludgeoning damage.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet>
            <description>Melee Weapon Attack: (Strength modifier + your proficiency) to hit, reach 5 ft., one target. Hit: 12 (1d12 + STR + souls) bludgeoning damage.</description>
        </sheet>
    </element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Transfiguration Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_TRANSFIGURATION" />
	<element name="Alteration Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_ALTERATION" />
	<element name="Body Clone Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_BODY_CLONE" />
	<element name="Soul Multiplicity Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_SOUL_MULTIPLICITY" />
	<element name="Domain Expansion: Self-Embodiment of Perfection Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_IDLE_TRANSFIGURATION_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_SELF_EMBODIMENT_OF_PERFECTION" />
</elements>
