<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="6.0.0">
			<file name="limitless.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innate-techniques(archetypes)/limitless.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="Limitless" type="Archetype" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_LIMITLESS">
		<supports>Innate Technique</supports>
		<description>
			<p>Are you the strongest because you larp, or do you larp because you are the strongest.</p>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_INFINITY" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_TELEPORTATION" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_OFFENSIVE_INFINITY" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_UNLIMITED_VOID" />
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>A technique whose power is only matched by its complexity, Limitless allows manipulation over space.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_INFINITY" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_TELEPORTATION" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_OFFENSIVE_INFINITY" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_UNLIMITED_VOID" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Infinity" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_INFINITY">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_INFINITY</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Beginning at 1st level, you gain the ability to use your manipulation over space to protect yourself effectively. As a bonus action for 1 Cursed Energy, you can encase yourself in a field of mathematical infinity costing 1 Cursed Energy at the start of your turn. When you are targeted by a weapon, spell, Cursed Energy attack roll or any saving throws from sources outside your body you roll a d6. On a 4 or higher, any attacks or spells made against you automatically fail to touch or harm you in any physical way. At 6th level, this becomes 3 or higher, and 2 or higher at 11th level.</p>
            <p class="indent">You can spend 1 Cursed Energy to automatically roll a 6 on an Infinity roll. At 11th level, you can spend 2 Cursed Energy at the beginning of each of your turns to automatically roll a 6 on Infinity rolls and you can activate Infinity as a reaction to being targeted by an attack or effect that you can see.</p>
            <p class="indent">When you take the Dodge action while Infinity is activated, you gain advantage on the d6 roll, and you can grant its benefits to any creatures within your reach.</p>
            <p class="indent">This feature does not work against poison or attacks that you cannot see until 6th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Bonus Action" usage="CE">
			<description level="1">For 1 Cursed Energy, you can encase yourself in infinity, costing 1 Cursed Energy at the start of each turn. When you are targeted by a weapon, spell, Cursed Energy attack roll or any saving throws from sources outside your body you roll a d6. On a 4 or higher, any attacks or spells made against you automatically fail to touch or harm you in any physical way. You can spend 1 Cursed Energy to automatically roll a 6 on an Infinity roll. When you take the Dodge action while Infinity is activated, you gain advantage on the d6 roll, and can grant its benefits to any creatures within your reach. This feature does not work against poison or attacks that you cannot see.</description>
            <description level="6">For 1 Cursed Energy, you can encase yourself in infinity, costing 1 Cursed Energy at the start of each turn. When you are targeted by a weapon, spell, Cursed Energy attack roll or any saving throws from sources outside your body you roll a d6. On a 3 or higher, any attacks or spells made against you automatically fail to touch or harm you in any physical way. You can spend 1 Cursed Energy to automatically roll a 6 on an Infinity roll. When you take the Dodge action while Infinity is activated, you gain advantage on the d6 roll, and can grant its benefits to any creatures within your reach.</description>
            <description level="11">For 1 Cursed Energy, you can encase yourself in infinity, costing 1 Cursed Energy at the start of each turn. When you are targeted by a weapon, spell, Cursed Energy attack roll or any saving throws from sources outside your body you roll a d6. On a 2 or higher, any attacks or spells made against you automatically fail to touch or harm you in any physical way. You can spend 1 Cursed Energy to automatically roll a 6 on an Infinity roll. You can spend 2 Cursed Energy at the beginning of each of your turns to automatically roll a 6 on Infinity rolls until the start of your next turn and can activate Infinity as a reaction to being targeted by an attack or effect that you can see.When you take the Dodge action while Infinity is activated, you gain advantage on the d6 roll, and can grant its benefits to any creatures within your reach.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Lapse Blue" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 3rd level, you can create another impossible concept, negative numbers which manifests as negative space. As an action for CE up to your modifier, you pick an unoccupied space within 30 feet you can see and create a 5 ft sphere until the beginning of your next turn as space corrects itself. This pulls creatures within a radius of 5 feet for each CE spent, forcing a Strength saving throw. On a failure, they take 2d8 + 1d8 for each CE in force damage and are dragged into the blue and grappled. At 6th level, on a failure of 5 or more they take maximum damage and are restrained. On a success they take half as much damage. A creature can repeat the save at the end of their turn.</p>
            <p class="indent">When you spend at least 5 CE on Blue, you can use its Maximum Output form to make it last for up to a minute. As bonus action, you can move the sphere 30 ft in any direction. All creatures currently stuck in the sphere are also moved and a creature that starts their turn in range must make the saving throw. You can dispel this technique as a free action.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description level="1">For up to {{ce:modifier}} cursed energy, you pick an unoccupied space within 30 feet you can see and create a 5 ft sphere until the beginning of your next turn. This pulls creatures within a radius of 5 feet adding 5 feet for each CE spent, forcing a Strength saving throw. On a failure, they take 2d8 + 1d8 for each CE spent in force damage and are dragged into the blue and grappled. When you spend at least 5 cursed energy on Blue, you can use its Maximum Output form to make it last for up to a minute. As bonus action, you can move the sphere 30 ft in any direction. All creatures currently stuck in the sphere are also moved and a creature that starts their turn in range must make the saving throw. You can dispel this technique as a free action.</description>
            <description level="6">For up to {{ce:modifier}} cursed energy, you pick an unoccupied space within 30 feet you can see and create a 5 ft sphere until the beginning of your next turn. This pulls creatures within a radius of 5 feet adding 5 feet for each CE spent, forcing a Strength saving throw. On a failure, they take 2d8 + 1d8 for each CE spent in force damage and are dragged into the blue and grappled. On a failure of 5 or more they take maximum damage and are restrained. On a success they take half as much damage. A creature can repeat the save at the end of their turn. When you spend at least 5 cursed energy on Blue, you can use its Maximum Output form to make it last for up to a minute. As bonus action, you can move the sphere 30 ft in any direction. All creatures currently stuck in the sphere are also moved and a creature that starts their turn in range must make the saving throw. You can dispel this technique as a free action.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Teleportation" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_TELEPORTATION">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_TELEPORTATION</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 6th level, your control over blue and space manipulation has increased. As an action, you can teleport yourself or another willing creature you touch 10 feet per Cursed Energy used.</p>
            <p class="indent">You can teleport an additional creature by doubling the cursed energy cost. Additionally, with the use of a binding vow, you can instead teleport a creature to a 5 ft circle you have prepared. You can teleport a willing creature you touch to one of these circles as an action for 5 cursed energy. You can only have one circle per binding vow.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
            <description>You can teleport yourself or another willing creature you touch 10 feet per Cursed Energy used. You can teleport an additional creature by doubling the cursed energy cost. With the use of a binding vow, you can instead teleport a creature to a 5 ft circle you have prepared. You can teleport a willing creature you touch to one of these circles as an action for 5 cursed energy. You can only have one circle per binding vow.</description>
        </sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Offensive Infinity" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_OFFENSIVE_INFINITY">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_OFFENSIVE_INFINITY</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 11th level, you have learned to push infinity to an aggressive mode through offensive training. As an action, you can spend CE up to your Cursed Energy modifier to amplify Infinity. All creatures within 10 ft must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, they are forced 10 ft directly away from you and take 2d8 force damage per cursed energy spent. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed away. </p>
            <p class="indent">If used at Maximum Output, a creature within 5 ft makes this save at disadvantage.</p>
            <p class="indent">Alternatively, you can choose one target within 5 ft of you and 10 ft away from a wall or solid structure, and spend CE up to your CE modifier as an action to crush them against it. The target must make a Strength saving throw, being forced against the wall and taking 3d8 Force damage for each Cursed Energy spent and be restrained until the start of your next turn on a failed save. On a success, they are pushed 5 ft back and take half as much damage. If you are more than 10 ft away from the target, the technique ends.</p>
            <p class="indent">If used at Maximum Output, you can spend CE up to your modifier at the start of your turn to maintain the technique, forcing the creature to repeat the save.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action" usage="CE">
			<description>You can spend up to {{ce:modifier}} cursed energy to force all creatures within 10 ft must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, they are forced 10 ft directly away from you and take 2d8 force damage per cursed energy spent. On a successful save they take half as much damage and are not pushed away. If used at Maximum Output, a creature within 5 ft makes this save at disadvantage. Alternatively, you can choose one target within 5 ft of you and 10 ft away from a wall or solid structure, and spend up to {{ce:modifier}} CE as an action to crush them against it. The target must make a Strength saving throw, being forced against the wall and taking 3d8 Force damage for each Cursed Energy spent and be restrained until the start of your next turn on a failed save. On a success, they are pushed 5 ft back and take half as much damage. If you are more than 10 ft away from the target, the technique ends. If used at Maximum Output, you can spend CE up to your modifier at the start of your turn to maintain the technique, forcing the creature to repeat the save.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Domain Expansion: Unlimited Void" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_LIMITLESS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_UNLIMITED_VOID">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_UNLIMITED_VOID</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Finally, at 18th level you have learned how to expand your own domain, showing the dangers of the Unlimited Void. You can create a void in space that causes victims to receive all kinds of stimuli and information endlessly, restricting their thought processes and actions. At initiative 20, every creature within your domain that is not touching you must make an Intelligence saving throw. On a failure, they take 12d8 psychic damage, their Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores become 1 and they are unable to cast spells, attack, use magic items, understand language, or communicate in any intelligible way, and fall unconscious for 1 minute. At the end of every minute, the creature can repeat this saving throw, ending these effects on a success. This effect can also be ended by Greater Restoration or Wish.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>At initiative 20, every creature within your domain that is not touching you must make an Intelligence saving throw. On a failure, they take 12d8 psychic damage, their Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores become 1 and they are unable to cast spells, attack, use magic items, understand language, or communicate in any intelligible way, and fall unconscious for 1 minute. At the end of every minute, the creature can repeat this saving throw, ending these effects on a success. This effect can also be ended by Greater Restoration or Wish.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_JJK_CLASS_FEATURE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION">
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Infinity Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_INFINITY" />
	<element name="Lapse Blue Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_LAPSE_BLUE" />
	<element name="Telportation Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_TELEPORTATION" />
	<element name="Offensive Infinity Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_OFFENSIVE_INFINITY" />
	<element name="Domain Expansion: Unlimited Void Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_LIMITLESS_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_UNLIMITED_VOID" />
</elements>
