<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<update version="6.0.1">
			<file name="miracle.xml" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/VortexTechK/JJK-Aurora/refs/heads/main/innate-techniques(archetypes)/miracle.xml" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="Miracle" type="Archetype" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_MIRACLE">
		<supports>Innate Technique</supports>
		<description>
			<p>I JUST HIT THE JACKP- oh wait wrong character.</p>
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DEADLY_MIRACLE" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE" />
			<div element="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_LUCK_OF_THE_DRAW" />
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>Your technique erases your memory of everyday little miracles to store them for when needed.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES" level="1" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME" level="3" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DEADLY_MIRACLE" level="6" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE" level="11" />
			<grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_LUCK_OF_THE_DRAW" level="18" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Little Miracles" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Starting at 1st level, your technique brings you strength when you witness good fortune. When you witness this, you gain a Miracle. You can have up to six Miracles at once, which are stored as marks somewhere on your body. You gain 2 Miracles for every miracle you witness at 11th level and 3 Miracles at 18th level.</p>
            <h5 class="caption">MIRACLES</h5>
                <table>
                    <thead>
                        <tr><td>Miracle</td><td>Description</td></tr>
                    </thead>
                    <tr><td>Lucky!</td><td>Everyone loves a Jackpot! When you or an ally you can see rolls the maximum amount on a roll, you gain a Miracle.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Equal Numbers!</td><td>Equal Numbers are supposed to be lucky, right? When you or an ally you can see rolls two equal numbers one after the other, you gain a Miracle.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Treasure!</td><td>Finding free stuff is always cool! When you or an ally you can see find an item worth $1,000 or more, you gain a Miracle.</td></tr>
                    <tr><td>Overcoming Hardship</td><td>Overcoming hardship is something rare in this harsh world, so every chance we get is a miracle. When you or a creature you can see succeeds on a roll they had disadvantage on, you gain a Miracle.</td></tr>
                </table>
            <p><strong>Blind Luck: </strong></p> Once per round when you take damage, you can spend a Miracle to reduce the incoming damage by Xd4 equal to your CE modifier. You add your proficiency bonus to the rolled amount and reduce the damage by that much. You can also do this as a reaction for a Miracle and 1 CE. When used this way, the d4 increases to a d6 and you add your proficiency bonus twice.
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>When you witness a miracle, you gain {{miracle:gain}} Miracle. You can have up to six Miracles at once, which are stored as marks somewhere on your body. A miracle occurs when you or an ally you can see rolls the maximum amount on a roll, rolls two equal numbers one after the other, finds an item worth $1,000 or more, or succeeds on a roll they had disadvantage on.</description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <grant type="Archetype Feature" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_BLIND_LUCK" />
            <stat name="miracle:gain" value="1" level="1" bonus="miracle" />
            <stat name="miracle:gain" value="2" level="11" bonus="miracle" />
            <stat name="miracle:gain" value="3" level="18" bonus="miracle" />
        </rules>
	</element>

    <element name="Blind Luck" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_BLIND_LUCK">
        <description>
            <p>Once per round when you take damage, you can spend a Miracle to reduce the incoming damage by Xd4 equal to your CE modifier. You add your proficiency bonus to the rolled amount and reduce the damage by that much. You can also do this as a reaction for a Miracle and 1 CE. When used this way, the d4 increases to a d6 and you add your proficiency bonus twice.</p>
        </description>
        <sheet action="Reaction" usage="Miracle">
            <description>When you take damage, you can spend a Miracle to reduce the incoming damage by {{ce:modifier}}d4+{{proficiency}}. You can also do this as a reaction for a Miracle and 1 CE. When used this way, the d4 increases to a d6 and you add {{miracle:blind:luck}} instead of {{proficiency}}.</description>
        </sheet>
        <rules>
            <stat name="miracle:blind:luck" value="proficiency" />
            <stat name="miracle:blind:luck" value="proficiency" />
        </rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Miraculous Outcome" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 3rd level, you can self-consciously alter fate. As a reaction to failing a roll you can spend 1 Miracle and 1 CE to add a d6 to the roll, potentially turning it into a success. This increases to a d8 at 6th level and a d10 at 11th level.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Reaction" usage="Miracle + CE">
			<description>As a reaction to failing a roll you can spend 1 Miracle and 1 cursed energy to add a d{{miracle:miraculous:outcome}} to the roll.</description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <stat name="miracle:miraculous:outcome" value="6" level="3" bonus="miraculous outcome" />
            <stat name="miracle:miraculous:outcome" value="8" level="6" bonus="miraculous outcome" />
            <stat name="miracle:miraculous:outcome" value="10" level="11" bonus="miraculous outcome" />
        </rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Deadly Miracle" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DEADLY_MIRACLE">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_DEADLY_MIRACLE</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 6th level, you have learned that out of difficulties, miracles grow. Your technique lets you fend off death by some miracle. When you are hit by an attack or fail a saving throw that would reduce you to 0 hit points or kill you outright, you can spend 2 Miracles and 2 CE to instead succeed the save or survive the attack and take no damage or additional effects. Completely escaping harm by seemingly dumb luck. While you have at least 1 Miracle, you make death saving throws at advantage.</p>
            <p class="indent">At 11th level, you can use this feature against an attack or effect that would reduce you to 1/2 or below your hit point maximum.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
            <description level="6">When you are hit by an attack or fail a saving throw that would reduce you to 0 hit points or kill you outright, you can spend 2 Miracles and 2 cursed energy to instead succeed the save or survive the attack and take no damage or additional effects. While you have at least 1 Miracle, you make death saving throws at advantage.</description>
            <description level="11">When you are hit by an attack or fail a saving throw that would reduce you to anywhere below half max hit points, you can spend 2 Miracles and 2 cursed energy to instead succeed the save or survive the attack and take no damage or additional effects. While you have at least 1 Miracle, you make death saving throws at advantage.</description>
        </sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Fated for Fortune" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 11th level you realize there is no bad future for you, only a path to fortune paved with miracles! If you roll 20 or higher using Miraculous Outcome, it is considered a critical success as if you had rolled a natural 20. You cannot land a Black Flash or gain a Miracle this way.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet>
			<description>If you roll 20 or higher using Miraculous Outcome, it is considered a critical success as if you had rolled a natural 20. You cannot land a Black Flash or gain a Miracle this way.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Domain Expansion: Luck of the Draw" type="Archetype Feature" source="JJK" id="ID_JJK_ARCHETYPE_FEATURE_MIRACLE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_LUCK_OF_THE_DRAW">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_LUCK_OF_THE_DRAW</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>Finally at 18th level you have mastered your technique allowing you to expand your domain. Your domain costs 2d20 CE to expand and lasts for 1d4 minutes. If you lack the Cursed Energy to expand your domain, you must reattempt on your next turn and reroll the 2d20. If you expand your domain as a reaction to another Domain Expansion, you can choose to spend 20 CE or to roll 2d20.</p>
            <p class="indent">At initiative 20, you gain 3 Miracles and have no limit on your max amount of Miracles. Within your domain, you can spend a Miracle on yourself or another creature when they make an attack or use a technique to imbue it with your domain's guaranteed hit.</p>
		</description>
        <sheet action="Action + Bonus Action + Movement" usage="CE">
			<description>For 2d20 cursed energy, at initiative 20, you gain 3 Miracles and have no limit on your max amount of Miracles. Within your domain, you can spend a Miracle on yourself or another creature when they make an attack or use a technique to imbue it with your domain's guaranteed hit. If you lack the Cursed Energy to expand your domain, you must reattempt on your next turn and reroll the 2d20. If you expand your domain as a reaction to another Domain Expansion, you can choose to spend 20 CE or to roll 2d20. Your domain lasts for 1d4 minutes.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Little Miracles Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_LITTLE_MIRACLES" />
	<element name="Miraculous Outcome Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_MIRACULOUS_OUTCOME" />
	<element name="Deadly Miracle Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_DEADLY_MIRACLE" />
	<element name="Fated for Fortune Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_FATED_FOR_FORTUNE" />
	<element name="Domain Expansion: Luck of the Draw Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_MIRACLE_DOMAIN_EXPANSION_LUCK_OF_THE_DRAW" />
</elements>
